Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Good evening, good day everybody and
welcome back to the Ask Ajit show. This
is once again an emergency session,
emergency episode of the show because we
are at war. We are at war with Pakistan
and a lot is happening. So in
yesterday's live stream, I had said that
I will do the next live stream on
Saturday as
scheduled. But it clearly um it's
important that we do it today because so
much is happening and while we were
doing the live stream yesterday, there
was a whole lot of action happening. The
Pakistan is trying to take out Indian
targets and so on. So let us discuss
more of the situation and before we do
that I'm going to see who all is on the
live chat. I can see Dongar Singh Johan
ICBMs Oscar Maris Dea Deayan Basu Vamshi
Ready MP Abid Nav Aurora V N Mali
Malcani Adjut Hunter Canvi Yam P Billy
Maguire Bully Maguire Geopolitical Dubai
Suna Spandan Kandelwal Rahul Sharma and
lots and lots of other people. So, let's
go and I'm going to take questions from
the live chat today. How about that? U
Oscar Madison from Texas. So, I'm going
to take questions from the live chat.
I've not had the time to sit down and go
through all the questions in the
comments and select the best questions.
I've not had the time to do that. So,
the questions that you've asked the
comments, I will uh look at them
tomorrow in tomorrow's uh live stream.
But uh today we're going to do it
entirely from the live chat. So, let's
take questions from the live chat. Uh
let's see what questions do we have.
Wamshi Reddi from Twitter says no
Karachi attack happened then. Well,
we'll wait and watch. Uh apparently no
Karachi attack has happened. Yesterday
there were all kinds of rumors on social
media. Um that apparently we have taken
out the port of Karachi and INS Vikrant
is in actions is in action. I'm not sure
how these rumors end up on social media.
I have nothing against rumors in in
during wartime even rumors can be a
weapon that we can use against the
adversary which is fine. Uh but as far
as uh we see uh it it doesn't look like
Karachi port has been taken out. Uh at
least we haven't made any such claims.
We as in the government of India right?
So today there was a press conference by
the government of India couple of hours
ago and we got some more details out of
it. And uh a lot has happened in the
last 48 hours, right? U it all started
with uh it all it all it all started
with uh the terrorist attack on uh
civilians on tourists in Pahelgam. And
we India we gave Pakistan about two
weeks to bring the uh terrorists to
justice and to shut down its terror
factory and Pakistan took no action. And
they actually made claims that somehow
it had India was responsible for this in
in some strange perverted way the the
way the only the Pakistani mind can
work. So we waited we gave them time to
uh deal with the situation to to bring
the terrorists to justice. They did
nothing. And then a couple of days ago
we launched uh pinpoint strikes on
Pakistani terror infrastructure. And
this time we recorded everything on
video. We filmed everything. We sent
loitering drones that went there and
filmed everything all the strikes and we
presented the evidence to the world in
respon. So so we took out their
terrorist
infrastructure, their terrorist
machinery. We took that out. In
response, they started shelling
civilians and they they tried targeting
Indian cities. Um the night of the 7th,
was it the night of the 7th of May? They
tried targeting 15 Indian cities with
missiles and drones. And every single
missile and drone was intercepted. Not a
single hit on an Indian target, whether
it was a civilian target or military
target. So then they started shelling uh
civilians in um on the Indian side of
the border of of the LOC u rajori punch
Uri and Indian civilians are suffering
as a consequence they're dying when
you're doing shelling you can't take
that out with anti-aircraft weapons
right so they've been doing that and we
have suffered casualties right so this
is another provocation by Pakistan this
is nothing short of terrorism if you are
shelling civilians and civilians are
dying and civilian property is being
destroyed and damaged that is terrorism.
Terrorism means what's the definition of
terrorism? It means you're targeting
civilians. So the Pakistanis are right
now as we speak indulging in more
terrorism. And then we responded again
by taking out Pakistani military
installations this time in broad
daylight using uh various kinds of uh
weapons uh mostly u kami khazar drones
what's called kami khazar drones the
harop drones or whatnot and we did this
in broad daylight and then the
Pakistanis last night I think they tried
attacking about more than 20 Indian
cities 20 or 25 Indian targets all the
way from lei in the north to Gujarat the
sir creek and buja region in the
south. Imagine trying to target a city
like Lei, a beautiful, calm, peaceful
city full of innocent
people. I mean, it's just
crazy. And today we did did a press
conference in which we uh uh our
government did the press conference in
which we they put all of this out. This
is what happened overnight. This is what
the Pakistanis have been trying. And
yesterday I said that we are a nation at
war. I said that and I stand by what I
said. We are a nation at war. Uh the
Pakistanis are trying their best to to
uh hit Indian targets. They want to hit
Indian civilians. They're trying to hit
Indian cities. They're trying to hit hit
civilian airports. They're also trying
to hit some military targets. But their
major target target the category of
target is civilian targets. standard
Pakistani terrorist mindset. Uh so that
is what's happening right now as we
speak. So we are in a state of in a
state of war. We are in a state of war.
We are at war with Pakistan. Now today's
press conference by the government of
India was very calm and it was kind of
deescalatory like we don't want any more
of this. If Pakistan keeps trying to
escalate we will certainly respond but
if they stop then you can consider the
case to be closed. That's the kind of
messaging we
gave right. So now the ball is in
Pakistan's court. Essentially we are
giving them an
offramp. The question is will Pakistan
take this opportunity to end the matter.
The answer is no. They won't. And that's
the problem which is why I reiterate
that we are at war with Pakistan.
There's also news, my friends. There's
also news that that came out and then it
was
that was quietened down. There's news
that at least three Pakistani fighter
planes were taken
out, right? That news came out the past
48 hours. At least three Pakistani
fighter planes. But has the government
of India said anything? I mean, here's
this question by MP. Is it true that
F-16 was not actually shot
down? Well, what actually happened? H
did we take out fighter planes? F F-16s,
JF17s, one heard that at least three
were taken out and then the news went
quiet. What happened? See, it's like
this. Please understand the Pakistani
psychology, the Pakistani mindset.
During the Cargill war, they sent their
soldiers disguised as tribals to fight
India. And when these soldiers were
killed, naturally they'll kill if
they'll be killed if they fight India.
When the soldiers were killed, the
Pakistani military refused to reclaim
their bodies saying that these are not
our
soldiers. Shameless people, shameful
behavior. These are your soldiers who
have died fighting for for your cause
and you are not even willing to reclaim
the bodies and give them a decent uh
proper honorable funeral. So that's what
Pakistan does. If they lose personnel,
they disown them. Why am I saying all
this?
Hypothetically, Pakistan uh loses two or
three fighter planes. Let's say they
lose three fighter planes and and
hypothetically India captures one
fighter pilot alive. Hypothetically,
consider the
scenario. So if we claim that we have
shot down three fighter planes and we
show the evidence then Pakistan has
nothing nowhere to hide, right? But if
we don't claim that we have taken out x
number of fighter
planes then Pakistan will try and hide
it that we lost anything. So then what
we can do in this completely fictitious
scenario in this fictitious scenario
what we can do now is that we can
quietly take our time and interrogate
that fire fighter pilot as long as we
need and get all the information out of
him or them.
Okay, we don't claim that we have shot
down fighter planes. We don't we don't
want that glory. We want the
intel. How is that scenario? Does it
sound good to you? I'm I'm just painting
a completely fictitious hypothetical
picture. So, uh let's keep it at that,
shall we? Okay. All right. So, now
Dongar Singh Johan raises a pretty
relevant point. What is wrong with
Turkey? Turkey. So the Turkish uh what's
his name? Erdogan he's the prime what
president of Turkey. Yes the president
of Turkey Erdogan has uh put out a tweet
in his Turkey language in which he has
spoken about the war between Hindustan
and Pakistan right and he has said that
it's unfortunate and we need to what
deescalate is the word going out on
social media. He says we need to
deescalate h both sides need to
deescalate and he says that the people
of Turkey stand with the brotherly
nation of Pakistan but they don't stand
with
India and in today's press conference g
given by the government of India it
emerged that the Pakistanis launched
between 400 to 500 drones at Indian
targets last night and most of these
apparently were Turkish drones.
Okay. So the Turks have been
u supplying the Pakistanis with drones
with weapons which the Pakistanis are
trying to use to to bleed India. They
they're failing thus far. Uh but that's
the situation. So what's wrong with
Turkey? Everything is wrong with Turkey.
Like I've said in the past, Turkey
doesn't have a history. Turkey has a
criminal record. It's a it's it's
exactly the same kind of country that
Pakistan is. Okay? Just the color of
skin is different. The Turks are
converted Greeks and the Pakistanis are
converted
Indians. But you see the similarity
there. So they're going to stand with
Pakistan and they obviously hope to get
something out of this. Hopefully some
nuclear technology or something or the
other. And um obviously the the the
hatred for the for for the non-believer,
the disbeliever, the the infidel is
there. So that's what's wrong with
Turkey and this is to be expected. So
Pakistan got a boost shot in the arm,
right? Turkey, the president of Turkey
came out in public and gave a statement
in favor of Pakistan, in support of
Pakistan and indirectly
uh uh you know critical of India. So
nothing surprising about this. Nothing
surprising about it. Okay, let's see
more
questions. Uh Kumar Patel says, "Do we
have the best air defense grid? How did
we protect uh subcontinent-sized nation?
How is it compared to the US, China,
Israel defense system?" Oh, there's no
comparison. It's very different. Every
nation is different. Every geography is
different. Every challenge, every
defensive challenge is different. Do we
have the best air defense grid? I
wouldn't say we have the best defense
grid air defense grid but we we clearly
have a super competent air defense grid
everything the Pakistan is lobbed at us
from the sky whether it's missiles or
rockets or drones everything has been
taken out and the Indian media is
reporting we have the S400 and the S400
took everything out these people have no
idea what they're talking about the S400
doesn't exist to take out drones
The S400 is therefore a very specific
set of threats and that's the kind of
threats it neutralizes. It's not it's
it's its purpose is not to neutralize
drones and and and rockets and
shells. The purpose of the S400 is to
take out very big threats like fighter
planes. Okay. It has a radius of
coverage of 400
kilometers and uh so it essentially can
cover most of
Pakistan because Pakistan would you like
to see the geography of
Pakistan. Let's see how wide the nation
is, how much strategic depth the nation
has. So here's the map of Pakistan.
Let's say you have an S400 sitting
somewhere here. So let's uh see how wide
the nation is from end to end about 500
kilometers. So you're safe from the
Sound and only if you're if you're far
in the west of Pakistan near near either
Afghanistan or near the Iran border,
right? You I think you're safest if
you're a Pakistani if you're sitting in
Baljasthan because then you have a
significant distance from any potential
S400 uh
system. Um so the S400 you can keep it
even a 100 kilometers inside Indian
territory and you can still take out any
Pakistani threat uh a fighter plane kind
of threat or potentially ballistic
missile threat. So the
S400 its purpose is to take out fighter
planes and short to medium range
ballistic missiles and also potentially
cruise
missiles. Its purpose is not to take out
drones. For those drones, we have other
air defense systems which have worked
brilliantly. So clearly India has really
surprised the world. Really surprised
the world that not a single Pakistani
uh rocket or missile or drone was to was
able to hit any substantial target in
India. And they have God knows they've
tried they've lobbed hundreds of these
weapons at us. So we have multiple
layers of air defense. The S400 is the
biggest one. We also have the Akash
missile which apparently has been the
superstar. Not the
S400. I'm not saying the S400 isn't
great. It's great. It's brilliant. But
the real superstar in the action of the
last 14 hours has been the Akash SAM
surfaceto-air missile and other systems
as well. So we have superb air defense
grid. Clearly, it's it's very obvious
now. It's very clear. The past 48 hours
has proven that. Uh but but please
understand there's a lot more to come.
We are at war and this is going to
continue. Um how do we how did we
protect the subcontinent size nation?
Look, the Pakistanis haven't tried
hitting targets deeper within India.
Okay. Thus far um so thus far we are uh
defending the border states essentially
which is uh Ladak, Jammu and Kashmir uh
Punjab, Rajasthan and Gujarat. That's
mainly the states we are defending and
they've tried hitting targets all across
these states. How do we compare it with
the US, China? Look, we can't compare.
Every nation is different so there's no
point comparing. Um look for example the
Israelis have the Iron Dome system which
is almost like a point defense system.
It's a very small tiny country compared
to India. So they can really saturate
the skies with Iron Dome missiles and
take out uh incoming bogeies
essentially. So it's a very different
set of scenarios.
Now Amisha says what's your take on JD
Vance's statement? JD Vance said that
the IndiaPakistan conflict is none of
the US's business. it has nothing to do
with us. We have no business talking
about it. Essentially, that's what he
said. I'm paraphrasing. I don't know
what exact words he used, but he said
that it's none of the US's business and
America needs to stay out of it. The
vice president of the United States said
that. So, what what should we infer from
that? What does it mean? It's obviously
a signal. It's not just uh an answer
giving given to a journalist who asked a
question. It's also a it's it's also
also a diplomatic signal. It's also a
policy statement. It's also a message to
India as well as Pakistan as well as
Russia as well as China and whoever else
is uh interested in whatever way. It's a
message. So how do we interpret what JD
Vance said?
What does it mean that this this
conflict this war is none of America's
business? Which is
surprising considering the history the
US has had with
Pakistan. The US was Pakistan's big
daddy in the 20th century. The US was
Pakistan's main funer and
financer. They are the ones who taught
Pakistan how to use terror as
uh as policy as state policy. It started
with the mujahedin in Afghanistan but it
also spilled out into into Punjab and
then into Kashmir in the 80s and
90s and then the primary the primary
target for Pakistani terror was India
all funded and financed by the US during
the war of sorry war on terror of George
W. Bush uh Pakistan was the lynchpin of
that. Uh it was the staging base for
whatever was was happening in
Afghanistan and so on. So the US has
been the big daddy for decades. Pakistan
was their wasal for decades. Then for a
decade or so Pakistan became China's vas
was vasal and then 2022 onwards for a
brief couple of years Pakistan was a US
wasal
again. Now what JD Vance has said
indicates that the US has washed its
hands of
Pakistan. It's essentially a statement
that means that India needs to handle
Pakistan whichever way it wants to. Just
ensure that this matter doesn't spill
out and become a bigger problem. Deal
with Pakistan whichever way you
want. That's the message. And why would
the US give such a message to
India? It's because the US is seriously
worried about China. And if they want to
contain China, which they're trying to
do, well, in the Eurasia region, the
only nation that is large enough to be a
significant bulvar against China and an
alternative to China is India. So they
need India on their side when it comes
to containing China. Now, we don't want
to be used as anyone's pawn. Obviously,
we are too big a nation, too old of a
civilization to be a pawn on someone's
chessboard.
But today, China is three and a half
times more powerful than us. And China
is not exactly a friendly nation. As I
think every Indian knows, China is a
threat. And right now they are three and
a half times more powerful than
India. So it makes sense to have some
kind of understanding with the
US, right? And that's why it makes sense
for us to be on the side of the US in
the matter that concerns China while
being completely independent and
sovereign and autonomous in other
matters. So when it comes to China, yes,
US and India, we're going to work
together on that. You want to do it
while using the quad quad route or other
route, Indo-acific, whatever, let's do
it. We'll work together on that. But if
you want us to oppose Russia, sorry.
Russia, India, that's a whole different
matter. You guys stay out of it. China,
we're going to help you. We're going to
be with you. Let's work together on
China. So, it's it's issue based
cooperation, but it is long-term
cooperation. So, India and the US are on
the same page when it comes to China.
And uh the US is trying to make good
with Russia's also. They tried at least
for a while. the trial uh but they will
not be able to make India uh pull away
from Russia or or abandon its you know
historic uh very positive relationship
with Russia. That's not going to happen.
So that's the deal. So when it comes to
Pakistan, the US is perfectly willing to
sacrifice Pakistan if it means that
India will be on the US's side when it
comes to the China matter. So it looks
like a deal has been struck. the art of
the deal. Deal with Pakistan. Take your
time. Do whatever you want. But you are
going to be with us when it comes to
China. So what does it mean in the
context of today's conflict? This is a
great question by
Amisha. It means most likely this is
going to go into in a certain direction.
U it
means that this conflict is not over.
See the
Pakistanis have done an incredibly
stupid thing. I said this two weeks ago
that the pahelgam pahelam attack is
going to go around in history as an
inflection point in Pakistan's history
and the day they did the attack was the
day the clock started ticking backwards
for them. Countdown began for
them. And I said the countdown could is
the clock is ticking down to zero. It
may last 10 years or 5 years or 3 years
or 6 months or 3
months. Now seeing the way the situation
is evolving the clock may countdown to
zero in 14
days possible. So as long as we manage
this properly, properly carefully and we
ensure the situation doesn't spill out
beyond the Indian subcontinent, the
Americans are okay with the
disintegration of
Pakistan. That's what it
means. All right, that's what it
means. Right, let us take some other qu
questions. Oh yeah, I had one question
that I taken from the comments. I I'll
answer that today and the u the others
I'll take it from the live chat. So
which question did I have? I had this
question by one of my older my old
viewers longtime viewers Chuching and
the question is are the far east states
of India in danger from Pakist from
China and Bangladesh in the current
scenario and this is a great question
you see India is a vast country and
India's far east is thousands of
kilometers away from Pakistan but you
know it's in a whole different
neighborhood India's far east is in
Southeast Asia let's take a look at the
map so when we talk about the Indian Far
East, we are referring to what everyone
calls the northeast. You see, if you
were to measure the distance from
Pakistan roughly to India's far east,
it's almost 2,000
km. If you were to talk about Nagaland
and the border with Pakistan, that's
over 2,000 km. So that's really far
away. So India's far east is actually
geographically situated in Southeast
Asia. It's the gateway to Southeast Asia
for us. And it's a very different part
of the country compared to the western
part of the country. And this is an
excellent question. Are these states you
know Arunachal Pradesh, Nagaland,
Manipur, Mizora, Megallaya, Tripura and
so on even Sikkim let's say uh and even
Bhutan let's consider are these states
in any kind of danger from China and
Bangladesh in the current scenario?
Uh yes, we will have to be very careful.
We will have to assume that there are
threats and let me tell you
why. See, right now, China is kind of
thus far staying out of this conflict.
They have made statements uh criticizing
India in regretting India's actions with
Pakistan, but uh they're not keeping a
very very very hawkishly close eye on
what's happening. Uh Mr. Xiinping is in
Moscow right now. He's he's attending
the victory day parade. I suppose it
must be over by now. Uh but you know if
it was a very precarious situation, Mr.
Xiinping would not be in Moscow. He
would he would be in Beijing anyhow.
So what is the threat that the far east
of India can face?
You may remember a few weeks ago the
Pakist I don't know who it was a
high-ranking Pakistani official whether
it's the foreign minister or the defense
minister or whatever it is I think it
was some kind of lady or something that
that high-ranking official Pakistani
official visited Bangladesh and right
now we are seeing a lot of
synergy between Pakistan and Bangladesh
they are essentially kind of on the same
page they are back to the days of East
Pakistan West Pakistan
Right? They both have governments and
regimes that see India as the enemy and
there is a shared hatred for India right
now among the people who rule east and
west
Pakistan and Pakistan right now is in is
kind of caught between a rock and a hard
place. India has hit them hard and the
Pakistani military needs to show
something to its people that you know we
were able to hit India back otherwise
they lose all legitimacy in the eyes of
their
people and if they lose legitimacy it's
going to be regime change it's going to
be disintegration of Pakistan there's
going to be riots on the streets and
they'll lose control so they need to
quickly do something the Pakistani
military that reassures that people
their people that look we hit back at
India now they are trying to lob
hundreds hundreds of missiles and drones
in India and everything is being shot
down. So what do they do? Well, what
they can do is to resort to what they do
best which is
terrorism. So I can assure you India
cities are on high alert. It may not be
visible but the governance machinery is
going to be and police machinery and
whatever other machinery we have will be
on high alert because it's well known
that there are you know when India
revoked the visas of all Pakistanis
after the balam attack we discovered
tens of thousands of Pakistanis who have
been living in India for
decades so they have plenty of people
who have infiltrated India I'm sure that
they we have not been able to catch all
of them and then there are Rohingyas
across India who have been settled in
Jammu and where god knows what places
and then there are there are millions of
Bangladeshes in India in illegal
infiltrators in 2014 there were there
were 50 billion according to the
government so imagine the threat we are
facing from
within so these
elements these enemies we have within
who are all across the country in every
city they're visible they're in your
face
That's a huge failure on the part of the
government of India. But look, this is
what this is today's situation. So these
elements can
be activated and leveraged to conduct
potential terror operations against
India clearly right now. Do we have the
presence of such elements in India's far
east?
Yes, we have Bangladeshes and Rohingyas
in all the far eastern
states. In Manipur, you have Bangladesh
and Rohingyas who have been allowed to
settle by the government. Why? I don't
know
why. In
Nagaland, I promise you these these
Bangladeshes are a big problem
today. They are all over all over the
place. I don't understand how they have
been allowed to
settle. I just don't get it. And as long
as these elements are present on Indian
territory, it's going to be a huge
problem. Half of Manipur is overrun by
foreign
cookies. They have killed more Manipuris
than the Pakistanis recently killed
tourists. But they don't matter.
Manipuris don't matter. The far east of
India doesn't matter apparently. So you
know this is a huge threat. These cookie
these chin cookies they have no
allegiance to India. These Rohingyas
they have no allegiance to India. These
Bangladeshies they have no allegiance to
India. These Pakistanis they have no
love or allegiance to India. They all
hate India. They can be leveraged by
foreign powers whether it is Bangladesh
or China or whoever. So yeah we we are
in
danger. We are in danger. As long as you
have foreigners squatting on Indian
territory, we are in danger. and the
government once it once we deal with
Pakistan or in parallel while dealing
with Pakistan we need to start evicting
foreigners out of India I don't care if
they're not willing to go throw them out
if Bangladesh is not willing to accept
them then I'm sure there are options the
geography of the Indian
subcontinent including our strategic
backyard is pretty large is all I will
say so it's high time the government
does something about this because yes uh
Chiching is asking a great question the
I think all states of India are in some
kind of danger from the mainly from the
enemies within who can be easily
controlled by the enemies
without Yes. So yes, the the security
agencies need to be on high alert
everywhere in in all the states that uh
have borders with other countries like
like
Bangladesh or whether it is Southeast
Asia, Burma which is in undergoing civil
war or whatever
else. Okay, let's take some more
questions
from Okay, good
question. Tjis says what's your
reply to some people who are asking for
for some Indian people who are clamoring
for
deescalation and how should Indians
prepare themselves for upcoming war
situations.
Um yeah there are Indians who are who
have the past 48 hours for the past 48
hours been clamoring for deescalation on
social media on X on Twitter and so on.
You know an I for an I will make the
world blind and we should deescalate.
There are people on both sides who are
suffering and so on and so forth.
Deescalation. I would like to take those
people know I would like to invite those
people. I invite those people to go to
the border with with Pakistan either at
the international border or at PK. Go to
Punch, go to
Rajori, go to Uri and and spend 48 hours
there.
Yes. And then ask India for
deescalation. When you're sitting there,
you'll find that there's incoming fire
towards you, missiles, shells, bullets
flying all over the place. So, are you
going to ask Mr. Modi for deescalation
or are you going to ask the Pakistanis
for deescalation? We are not the
aggressors. We did not start this. India
did not start this. We are at the
receiving end of terrorism and fire from
the Pakistanis. It is for Pakistan to
deescalate. It is not for India to
deescalate. Okay. Yes. Sure. The this
fighting is going to cause pain on both
sides. True. It's going to cause pain on
the Pakistani side if civilians get hit
inadvertently. We don't target civilians
but if civilians get civilians get hit
is going to cause pain and suffering on
that side. On our side we have been
having pain and suffering for
decades. Now the qu see the question is
who is causing this pain and
suffering? Who is causing it? Is it war
that's causing it or is it evil people
who are causing it? War happens because
of the actions of evil people, right?
And if you're at the receiving end, if
you're a victim of the of those actions,
then you have a choice. You either sit
and let it happen and you you absorb the
pain and suffering or you say enough and
I'm going to give the pain and suffering
back to the evil people. I think the
people the ones who are responsible for
all the pain and suffering are Pakistan.
And as long as Pakistan keeps existing
in the current shape and form, as long
as the ISI military terrorist entity,
combined entity keeps existing, pain and
suffering is going to be permanent as
long as this keeps existing. So we have
to take this entity out. We have to
liberate the world and the people of
Pakistan and the people of the Indian
subcontinent from the burden from this b
from the burden of this evil entity.
So that's what I would say to the
people, the Indian people who are asking
for deescalation. Please go to the line
of control, go sit there, go, go, go
live there for a couple of days. Then
you will know who actually needs to
deescalate, right? And if they don't
deescalate, we're going to make them
deescalate this time. We're going to
make them deescalate. This war is not
over. We are we are giving Pakistan the
option and you know you have an offramp
like the west likes to say stop whatever
you're doing and we're going to end this
year but Pakistan won't end this
year okay so this war is going to go to
to its conclusion territory will change
lines on the map is going to change now
the question is how should Indians
prepare themselves for the upcoming war
situations I would say look there's
nothing much you have to
just take basic precautions.
Um the main thing is you have to
unconditionally support your country. Um
and if you are on social media, if
you're a Twitter warrior or whatever, go
ahead and and have some fun on social
media. Um and yeah, that's what look the
government of India, the armed forces
are more than capable of taking care of
the country. There's nothing that
individual Indians need to do. Uh we pay
our taxes. the government of India has
more than enough funds and everything it
needs. Okay. Um we have adequate numbers
of soldiers and all that. So don't
worry. The only thing is you take
adequate precautions. Don't
uh don't
allow media rumors to mislead you. There
are many Indian media outlets that are
taking the side of Pakistan, right? And
so on. So support your country
unconditionally. Your country is right.
We are not a terrorist nation. We have
been on the receiving end of terror for
decades. For
decades and yeah, we're going to we're
going to dismantle Pakistan this time.
Enough is
enough. Duresh Palanchol says on the
21st of April, Apple announced its
production being moved from China to
India. Is this a war between India and
Pakistan a Chinese proxy against the
next globe global next economic
production house? Look
clearly this if this war does benefit
China. If this war has the effect of
making India look like an unstable
country, a country that is not a good or
sound investment
destination, then it's a win for China.
It's a big win for China, right? So it's
pretty clear that this is the Chinese
must be happy right now. So what India
needs to do is we need to ensure that
this situation should not last more than
14 days and then the next next 14 days
um yeah whatever needs to happen needs
to happen. But you are right you know
these things are all all
interconnected. China sitting far away,
Beijing is far away. The border with
Tibet is right at our doorstep. Um, and
what's happening in visa v Apple in
China and India, it's all interconnected
with this current war with
Pakistan. T says no other option, no
option other than full-blown war, says
Pakistan's defense minister. Well, if
you want it, you can have it. You're
going to have
it. Harsha says, if we advance forward,
how do we secure the territory
permanently without losing it? Does
boots on the ground change the scenario
completely? Boots on the ground changes
the scenario completely. Uh how do we
secure the territory permanently without
losing it? Leave it to the armed forces.
They know how to do it. We don't need to
worry about it. The armed forces, it's
their job to do this. They're
professionals. They know how to do it.
No, we don't need to worry about that.
Um,
uh, Sorov Sor says, "Do we get a chance
to see the bramos in action?" The Brahos
may have been in action or maybe not. We
don't know. Look, this is not a live
cricket match that we're going to see it
ball by ball. A whole lot of stuff is
going to happen that we may not know for
years. The bramos may be in action, but
we may not get to see it. So we can see
this the test
firings.
Okay. Mr. 88 says the Pakistan defense
minister is quoted as saying we didn't
intercept Indian drones as it would have
given away our defense positions. What I
what I have my honest thoughts and
opinions on this master stroke strategy.
So listen, I'm sitting in in a place and
the drone is coming at me, right? the
suicide drone and I have an interceptor.
I have a system that can, let's say,
take out drones and it's coming really
fast. I can't really escape before it
hits. So, what should I
do? If I use the intercepting uh
technology, it'll give away the data and
the locations and defense positions to
the adversary. So, I'll not use it. I'll
die. Is it is it is that how it
works? In Lahore, the air defense system
was taken out by Indian drones, kamikazi
drones. So was it a sound
decision to not give away the defense
positions when the defense positions
were already known to
India? This is called
cope. This is called coping. you know,
making some kind of excuse to make it
sound like u you're actually winning
when you're when you're actually
losing. So, yeah, it's u it's a joke.
It's a nice
joke. Uh Kumar says, "The Turkish drones
failed. How will it will it affect the
Turkish drone market?" The world look
wherever there is a conflict the world
looks with a lot of interest not the lay
people of the world but people who are
in the defense industry people who are
um geopolitically aligned like you know
government officials military officials
u arms manufacturers potential arms
customers they all look at the action
that's happening with a great deal of
interest let's say I am a potential
consumer. Let's say I'm a potential
buyer of Turkish drones, then I would
like to very much observe what happens
when Turkish drones are used in actual
combat. You can use Turkish drones in
field trials and all that. That's fine.
You know, in cricket what they say
there's a world of difference between
net practice and actual match practice.
You can be in great form as a batsman in
the nets, middling every ball and
hitting everything perfectly, but that
doesn't mean you're going to do well in
in in live action. The per the
performance in the live action is what
matters more than your net performance.
Similarly, the performance of drones
during field trials and all is okay, but
how they perform in real wartime combat
scenarios is what really matters. That's
where uh the true uh value can be seen.
The value or lack of it can be seen. So
the Turkish drones were lobbed at us all
last night. 400 or 500 Turkish drones
were lobbed at us and every single one
of them was taken out
um through different
means. Some of those means were
non-kinetic means apparently. Yeah. So
the Turkish drones uh they failed. they
failed very
much. If you are a sensible buyer and
you want a system that actually performs
in combat, I would suggest you stay away
from Turkish drones. Byakar or whatever
it's called, Kizilma. Now, Kizilma is
different. But yeah. Yeah. So, the
Turkish drones have failed or whichever
drones that the Pakistanis had. So, it's
a blow to the reputation of the Turkish
uh drone industry.
Nikunju Sharma says, "Please tell how
the Indian Navy is going to take action.
How will our aircraft carrier be useful
in the battle?" Uh, I don't know. I
would actually prefer not to have the
aircraft carrier participate in the
battle. It can be at sea and defend the
coastline of India, but I don't think it
should be used in offensive in an
offensive manner. I think if you want to
have the Navy participate in the
war, then you can use submarine launched
u weapons or weapons that are launched
from standoff distances from um
destroyers or various other kinds of
warships. The weapon you want to use is
typically a cruise missile. And we have
one of the cruise missiles which is
called the Brahmos, right? And it's a
pretty good cruise missile, believe you
me. So uh I would want to have that sort
of uh involvement of the navy destroyers
or submarines launching cruise missiles
at wherever uh the targets are whether
it's Karachi or whatever it is that's
how it should
go. Um they just says seems like Modi G
will be the best PM even surpassing the
fame of Indra Gandhi. We have to wait
and watch. I think the next two weeks
are going to we'll decide how how it
goes,
right?
Okay.
Um, Mr. 88 says ex government affairs
account is openly lecturing us on
censorship and free speech nonsense for
banning 8,000 8,000 X accounts. Let them
do it. Let them do it. Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter. They do. They they'll do
that. They'll always, you know, try and
uh portray themselves as having the high
moral ground. We believe in free speech.
You believe in free speech. Yeah. During
Biden's regime, how many Americans were
blocked from Twitter? Permanently banned
from Twitter. H what happened to your
free speech? Then Donald Trump was
banned from Twitter and these clowns
want to lecture us when we do something
for the sake of national security. These
people are two-faced
hypocrites.
So what's appropriate for us to do? It's
appropriate for us to laugh at
them. Arian Rocking Gaming says Karachi
Port official ex account posted that the
port has been damaged. Later said that
nothing has happened and their account
was banned. Banned? It seems suspicious.
Are they hiding something? It's possible
they are hiding something but uh the
government of India has made no
statements about corruption
whatsoever. So in case we have done
something there perhaps possibly then we
are not taking any claim or credit for
it. So you know what India is doing?
India is being super unpredictable.
Nobody has any idea what what the
government of India is planning. Even
Indians have no idea what the government
of India is planning and what what is
the next step going to be
like right are we are we deescalating
are we
disengaging or do we have a surprise in
in plan surprise that's being planned
like 3 days from
now. So it's good to play the game this
way. Keep all options open. Make people
wonder what's coming next. Right.
So I don't know what's happened in
Karachi. Have we actually done something
there? Have
we done some military action in Karachi?
There were rumors last night of of
Karachi port being uh targeted in some
way apparently by the Indian Navy. But
but we haven't officially made any
statements. So let's wait and watch. I
think in a couple of weeks uh once the
dust settles we will know exactly what
happened. And I think a lot of people
were going to be surprised to know what
was going on all these days.
So okay.
Um okay. Avish Mishra says will there be
an official declaration of war and why
is Turkey showing interest in the
conflict especially with Turkish drones
being used? Uh we just discussed Turkey.
Erdogan loves Pakistan. Turkey and
Pakistan are very similar nations in a
lot of ways and it's natural for them to
show support for Pakistan and they have
this shared hatred for polytheists like
us and they have a shared hatred for
ancient civilizations
um and they have other things in common
as well. Both countries have a criminal
record not a history. They don't have a
history they have a criminal record. So
very similar they both have this
terroristic mindset and uh yeah so
that's why Turkey is showing interest in
the conflict and they seek to gain
something from Turkey as well from
Pakistan as well maybe nuclear
technology maybe something else right um
and Turkey has this ambition of being
the next leader of the Islamic world and
they want to revive the Ottoman Empire
and so on that sort of thing and their
drones have failed which is buhoo and
haha Now, will there be an official
declaration of war? There's no need to
de declare war
officially. This is not the 19th century
anymore. We declare war and then we
shall fight and then we shall march on
the field wearing red coats and we shall
walk in formation while the bullets are
flying and so on. No man, this is the
21st century. You don't have to declare
war. We are at war. We will not declare
war unless we do. That's for Mr. Modi to
decide. But we are at war. Please
understand that there's no need to fight
a war properly once there's an official
declaration. You keep saying every day
that we are trying to deescalate but the
Pakistanis are unwilling and we don't
want war but you fight the war. That's
the right way to do
it. Okay.
Uh Lero online says I saw a headline and
trending in social media that the
Baloistan u the people of Baluchistan
have declared themselves as a sovereign
country and they seek validation from
the UN and first world nation. What's my
take? Look uh I support this first of
all. I think I tweeted this yesterday
that it's an appropriate time. I I
tweeted that in the middle of the night
yesterday. I didn't sleep till 3:00 a.m.
last night, you know, with all this
action raging. So sometime in the night,
maybe 1:00 a.m. 2:00 a.m. I tweeted this
that this is an appropriate time for
Balojasthan to declare its independence.
And I don't care if it's just Twitter
accounts are doing it, but I think
everybody from Balojasthan who is on
social media, whether it's X or
whatever, they need to declare
Balojasthan's independence. Uh and
apparently there's something going on in
um in Baljasthan. What's the capital of
Balojasthan? The capital of Buljasthan
is Queta obviously and apparently the
Pakistan army is facing trouble in Queta
and maybe I heard rumors yesterday I
don't know if they're true that maybe
they've withdrawn from
Queta. So uh my point
is they should support Balojasthan
independence. If there are
uh headlines and reports in social media
that Balojasthan has declared declared
independence, we as individuals one
thing we can do is we can amplify their
voice on social media and uh voice our
support. So any any Twitter account who
is saying Balojasthan is independent and
it's free. We need to support it. We
need to amplify it, right? So that's the
least you can do. Send a tweet saying we
support Balojasthan's independence and
so on. That sort of thing. But has it
actually happened? I think it's too
early to know. I think Pakistan at this
point in time, the Pakistani army, ISI
terrorism, terrorist machinery, that one
unified entity, I think thus far they
are still in control of their country.
The longer this war drags on, the more
tenuous their hold on the country will
become. Okay? Because as long as they're
unable to inflict any damage on India
and they keep absorbing the damage which
is visible to the public, the longer
that
happens, the more their legitimacy will
be questioned in Pakistan. They'll if
your armed forces who are your
dictatorial overlord, they look
important and in and unable to justify
their rule over you. Then people are
going to overthrow them. That's the
direction in which this is
going. Okay. Swastik Mahesh says the
Balojasthan Liberation Army claims that
about 30% of Balojasthan area is
independent. Is it possible that after
the operation Synindur Baljasthan will
declare complete independence from
Pakistan? I think the Baljasthan
Liberation Army has already declared
long ago that Baljasthan is independent
and they're fighting for that
independence to make that make that
statement into reality. That's what
they're doing. Um it I think it's pretty
certain that about 30% at least of
Balachasan is not under the control of
the Pakistani military. Even if you look
at Kyber Paktuna, half of Kyber Pakuna
is
essentially independent. You know they
there is no rule of law of Pakistan in
about half of Kyber Pakuna. So I'm
pretty sure about 30% of Baluchasan is
lawless or they have their own law as
per their wishes. uh so I think that
should increase now and it is quite
possible that once the dust settles over
operation zindur and the ongoing war
it's pretty it's quite possible that
balasan may be independent it's pretty
possible
yeah they just says can we defeat
Pakistan and elect a puppet PM in
Pakistan in place of allowing it to
disintegrate into parts I think the best
way forward is uh to to have multiple
independent nations we can certainly do
it but it's a pain for
uh what should happen is each of these
provinces needs to be become
independent. Let Hinduh become
independent with the capital. Let
Minagar or Karachi it was called
Minanagar 2,000 years ago. It's today
called Karachi. So let be independent
with Karachi as the capital. Let
Baljasthan be independent with Queta as
the capital. Let Ky Pakunwa reintegrate
with Afghanistan with our blessings and
let Pakistan occupied Jammu and Kashmir
Gilgit Baltistan return to the fold of
mother India and let
Punjabistan exist for a while.
Right. Right. So and Debo says they are
attacking Pokan now. So I have a TV
screen behind behind this lens on the
other
side and something is happening in
Jesi something in Kupwara something in
Punch Baramula Uri Jammu and so on and
apparently Pran so Pran is in Rajasthan
they're attacking Pokran you see we are
signaling to the world my friends that
we want to
deescalate we have retaliated to a
Pakistani provoc ation and it should end
with that.
They punched us, they hit us and we hit
back and that should be enough. But then
they are trying to escalate. They're
trying over and over again to
escalate. So here's what what's going to
happen. We today we the press conference
the government gave today was a press
conference that was very calm and it
indicated our desire to end the matter
here right and we did not really hit it
hit hit any major Pakistan targets like
Karachi Lahour whatever yesterday
despite the and and today as well
despite the constant pro Pakistani
attempts to hit more than 20 Indian
cities
all
night. So, we have given them an
offramp, but now they're attacking Pokan
again, right? So, if this situation now
escalates and we respond twice as hard,
whose fault is it going to
be? You cannot be a
nation that hosts Osama bin Laden and
then gets to play victim. You can't be a
nation that that
that creates the
Taliban and then gets to play victim.
You can't be a nation that cuts off the
head of journalists like Daniel Pearl
and then gets to play victim. You can't
be a nation whose whose citizens fly
planes into buildings in New York City
and then you get to play victim.
So I think we need to remind the world
of this that Pakistan is a terrorist
nation and if they don't back down now
right now within the next 14 days
maximum the borders are going to
change. So yeah that's that's the
direction in which this is going. The
borders will
change. Okay. Two idiot NRIs says say
say or says I don't know say say say say
say say say say say say say say say say
say say say say say say say say reports
are that Pakistan has about 10 days of
ammunitions they're low running low on
fuel and naturally owesen money does
pressing this for more than 10 days keep
the advantage keep advantaging India
even more why 14 is the upper limit okay
you have raised a very important and
interesting
point Pakistan we know are always short
in cash they are nation that's one step
away from bankruptcy at any given day on
any given
day. Now this claim that you are making
and based on reports that you've heard
is that Pakistan has about 10 days of
ammunition, munitions, whatever left.
How credible is this
claim? I think it's pretty credible. Why
do I say this? In case you have been
paying attention at what's been
happening during Pakistan's vasage of
the US during the Biden regime days,
then you would have
noticed that Pakistan as a good vasal of
the US sent a lot of
ammunition to Ukraine.
They sent a lot of ammunition to Ukraine
to help uh the cause of the Ukraine war
as a good
little of the US. And today they find
themselves in the situation of their own
making where India is not now willing to
to let them off with a face saver.
Pakistan does not get a safe face saver.
The Pakistan ISI military terrorist
entity does not get a face saver. Aimir
does not get a face
saver. If you want to back down, you
will back down while being
humiliated. Otherwise, bring it
on. This time, India is going to be the
unpredictable actor. Historically, the
past 80 years, the Pakistanis have acted
like the proverbial madman in a very
calculated way by keeping on making
threats like they're
crazy. They forced India to to act like
like the same like the same sparring
partner. This time it's going to be the
other way around. This time it's going
to be very different and you're going to
see this the next couple of days, next
few days. Pakistan is not going to get a
face saver and they're not going to be
able to hit India and by chance if they
hit any civilian area in India they're
going to be they will they have no idea
what's coming for them. They have
absolutely no idea what's coming for
them and you are right they are running
out of ammunition. The Turks are sending
aircraft to Pakistan with some supplies.
Those supplies will not
last. Turkey we will remember what you
have been doing.
will remember what Turkey has been doing
and what role they have played and I
would urge my fellow Indians and all
civilized people. You know the
Mediterranean region is a beautiful
region. No question about it. You want
to visit the Mediterranean, you want to
visit the Agency, you want to visit the
Ionian islands, you want to do all that,
go to
Greece, go to Italy, go to
Sardinia. Yes. Go to Tuskani. Go to
Sicily. Visit the Greek islands. Visit
Cfalonia. Visit Greece. Visit Athens.
Visit
Sparti. Visit
roads. Visit Greece. Do not visit
Turkey. Okay? Do the world a favor. Do
the civilized world a favor. Turkey is
the European version of
Pakistan and Albania is the Albania is
the European version of Bangladesh.
Okay, you get it? So uh coming back to
the question yes Pakistan is running
short of munitions and the US is not
going to come to the rescue this time.
The Chinese may try to do something. Do
they have have enough time to turn the
tide for Pakistan? Can Turkey turn the
tide for Pakistan? Pakistan finds itself
caught between a rock and a hard place.
And the longer they keep this up, the
the more they're going to find
themselves running out of options.
That's what's going to happen the next
four, five, 6 days. In 7 days, there's
going to be panic stations in Pakistan
if this
continues. Okay. So that's the direction
in which this is going, which is which
is dangerous. So India is going to have
to play the game very well. We're going
to have to
manage the re rearrangement of the
furniture of Pakistan very very
carefully. Okay. Melon B says, "If
Pakistan is dismantled and Bulajasthan
comes into existence, what would our
relationship with the state be like,
what sort of geopolitical
advantage would we gain with
it? Gain from it?"
Um, look, we would have access to um
Guada first of all, if Balojasthan comes
into existence as a sovereign nation,
we're going to have a good relationship
with the people of Balojasthan. We're
going to help them. We're going to uh
aid in the reconstruction of the nation.
We will have projects for building for
constructing highways and railways and
and whatn not libraries and schools and
a parliament building like we have done
with Afghanistan. We will have the same
kind of relationship with Baljasthan
that we have with Afghanistan. Even the
Taliban like
India, even the Taliban have a have have
warm feelings to feelings towards India
because of our track record the past 30
40 years. It's not something like you
know the US comes in and gives some aid
for a for a few months and then
disappears. We have consistently
supported Afghanistan and the people of
Afghanistan. We have u you know we have
worked on projects. We have started
projects and done things that have
helped the common people of Afghanistan.
agriculture project projects, dams, uh
water canals, um the parliament
building, everything we have done helps
the common people, the common man, woman
and child of Afghanistan. Even
individual Taliban members, their
families have benefited from what India
has done, which is why nobody in
Afghanistan hates India. Despite them
being an Islamic nation, despite them
being uh the Taliban, they still can't
make themselves help hate India. and
India and Taliban regime are
cooperating. We have a good working
relationship. Now if Balojasthan comes
becomes a sovereign nation, we're going
to have a similar uh relationship with
with Balojasthan. Similar I mean
something similar to what we have with
Afghanistan. And we're going to help
them the same way we have helped
Afghanistan consistently for the past
few decades. So it's going to be a very
good relationship. We're going to help
them set up a a completely new nation,
right? And what geopolitical advantage
we gain? We get access to the Macran
coast. We can develop the port of
Guadada. We can have Guadada in addition
to Chabahar as a port of transport
shipment into Afghanistan and various
other places. So it's it's good. It's
good. It's a win-win for both nations
for Baljasthan as well as India. So
yeah, it could happen in the next couple
of weeks.
Um what else do we have? Nikonju Sharma
says what do you think will Pakistan
learn anything from this or are they
going to retain the same mindset and
they'll repeat what they always do. So
if you want to know
whether someone is going to learn from
what's happening now or whether they
will learn nothing and keep doing the
same thing, all you have to do to
predict predict the future is to look at
the past
history. All you have to do is look at
the past history. We have about roughly
80 years of Pakistan history, right?
Roughly slightly less than that. Before
that there was no Pakistan. It was part
of our our land, our our civilization.
So we have about 80 years of 80 years of
history to look back at. In the past 80
years have they ever learned from their
defeats? They have fought how many wars
with India? 47 48 that's one war. Then
65 that's two. 71 is three. Uh 99 is
four. And this is the fifth one. So
they've lo they've fought four wars with
us. They've lost every single war. 71
was devastating. It was a viv section of
Pakistan. Have they ever learned
anything from this? Have they changed
their ways? They have never learned a
thing. They have never changed their
ways. They've always doubled down on
fighting
India. As long as this entity exists,
it's going to keep behaving the same
way.
If we back down from what's happening,
we deescalate and let Pakistan get away
scot-free, then in two weeks time after
the war is over, this war, today's war,
in two weeks they will be going all over
social media, going all over the western
media saying that we actually won this
engagement. They will be claiming in in
two weeks time that we actually defeated
India in this engagement. We forced them
to back down. That's what they will be
claiming all across Western
media. And then they will double down on
terrorism. They'll they'll tell their
people that we actually defeated India.
We frightened India. We made India back
down. And now we're going to show them
who we
are. So as long as this entity exists,
they're going to behave this way.
They're going to behave the exact same
way. So they have this today, you know,
the the Pahelam attack was barbaric. It
was extraordinarily painful to see how
those people suffered, how the people
were shot, how those ladies were s
sitting and crying next to the bodies of
their relatives. Horrible
thing. But by doing this, Pakistan has
given
India a golden opportunity to end this
once and for all. And India should not
back down. The Pakistanis are not going
to back down. They're going to continue
the strikes on India.
So, so this is the
time everyone asks me in every I how
many ask sessions I've done. This is the
244th episode, right? In every episode
from episode 1 until today's episode,
episode 244, people have asked me when
is the right time to take back
P. This is the right
time. Okay. Uh, noisan says what about
Afghanistan? As they said, they would
support Pakistan if India takes any
action after the Palam attack. I am not
sure who in Afghanistan has said said
that. Uh, as far as I know and I've seen
the Taliban actually supported India uh
expressed support towards India after
the news of the Pahelgam attack came
out. The Taliban do not support
Pakistan. The the Taliban despise of
they despise Pakistan. They are pons. Do
you have any idea how much the Pashons
have suffered at the hands of the
Pakistanis? How much Afghanistan has
suffered at the hands of
Pakistan? Why is Afghanistan a war torn
devastated nation? Because of Pakistan.
The Pashons hate Pakistan and
Pakistan occupies a significant portion
of historical Pashon land which is what
what's called the Kyber Pakum province
of Pakistan KPK. So Pakistan and
Afghanistan have a deep
longstanding century and a half long or
older than that territorial
dispute. The Taliban are pashur
nationalists. They want the pashon
territory back and they have this blood
enmity with the Punjabis the Punjab
Pakistani
Punjabis. Afghanistan is not going to
support
Pakistan. Okay. Um and go and see on
social media what's what the reactions
of the Afghans are. I'm not going to ask
you to cherrypick the good reactions.
I'm going to tell you do a survey of
statistical survey of what is the kind
of reaction like take a 100 samples take
200 samples of Afghan reactions on
social media to the ongoing war with
between India and Pakistan who's
supporting whom? I assure you a majority
of Afghans pashons at least support
India and the pashons are the majority
population.
Uh, Dongar Sik Johan says, "Do you
really think doing blackouts in the age
of infrared goggles, thermal cameras,
and GPS does it really makes any sense?"
Well, it doesn't it doesn't hurt to take
extra precautions. I I know what you're
saying and I kind of agree with you
actually. But you know there's no harm
in taking extra precautions because see
Pakistan does have Turkish drones
which they have in limited
numbers and most modern drones you can
feed GPS coordinates into them and the
drone will just fly. Whether it's day or
night doesn't matter. Whether there's
light or not not doesn't matter. So
whether you black out your city or not
doesn't really matter if you have a
drone that has GPS coordinates fed into
it and is able to access GPS by by using
whatever means in that case your
blackout won't matter in case you're
firing a missile at someone and uh once
again if you can feed coordinates into
the into the missile it doesn't really
matter but we know that Pakistan is a
pretty primitive nation. Look, I'm not
saying India is a very advanced nation.
We are also a third world nation. But
compared if you compare India and
Pakistan and Pakistan is fourth world,
right? So if you look at the weapon
systems they have, not all of those
weapon systems are 21st century weapon
systems. Some of them could be pretty
primitive. So if you have a city that is
in that is blacked out, then maybe it
gives you a better chance. Maybe not all
of Pakistan's weapons use GPS. Maybe
some of them need visual confirmation of
the target. It always helps to take
extra precautions. It doesn't hurt at
all, right? Yeah. It's it's kind of an
inconvenience. The city is blacked out.
There's no power. You have to put the
curtains curtains on the windows and use
little light. Maybe there's no internet.
So, you can't
do scrolling of Instagram res. Okay.
Small price to pay. So, you're right
actually. But uh overall I think it
doesn't it doesn't hurt to take extra
precautions. Siligurian Dormon
says Siligurian Dormon if Pakistan falls
apart what happens to its nuclear
weapons and that's a big question. That
is the big question that we we're going
to have to address because it is
probably going to fall apart sometime
soon. So what happens to the nukes? I
think we're going to have to have a cons
contingency plan. Now, I can't give you
the answers, but the Indian military and
the Indian uh armed forces government,
they will probably have a plan for this.
How to secure the nukes before they
start floating around the world. We
don't want lose nukes. So, I am pretty
sure we have a very very clear idea of
where the nukes are. And I'm sure we
have multiple contingency plans, plan A,
plan B, plan C, multiple scenarios of
what to do when Pakistan starts breaking
apart. Maklavin says, "So Chinese air
defenses failed to stop her drones and
now apparently an intact Chinese missile
was found in Indian territory. Can we
say the Chinese weapons aren't really up
to the mark?" Uh, I think we can safely
say that.
Um so the Pakistanis have Chinese uh
radars and air defense systems and those
failed completely. Pakistan has been hit
at will by India not with supersonic
cruise missiles which are very hard to
stop by anyone but we have hit them with
loitering
drones subsonic drones right drones that
you can see coming in and screaming down
and then hitting the target and they
haven't been able to take these drones
out. Maybe they took a few drones out,
but we have scored multiple very, very
painful, damaging hits. We took out
Lahor's air defense system. We destroyed
so many of those terror infrastructure
buildings and whatnot. The headquarters
of the of the LA, we uh took out the the
terrorists who killed Daniel Pearl and
and so at least 100 more terrorists have
died. The Pakistani military gave them
state funerals. We have been able to hit
Pakistan at
will and the Pakistani air defenses
failed. And what's worse is that we sent
drones to film the
hits. So we had systems that were
targeting the terror infrastructure and
dropping bombs and missiles and whatnot
at these buildings. At the same time we
had drones which were loitering over the
over the area and filming what was
happening and the films have been put
out in the public domain and those are
that is evidence that cannot that is
that is incontrovertible. So we had
drones flying over Pakistan just
standing there essentially floating over
an area and filming the hits
calmly and the Pakistanis were not able
to take those drones out.
So what's very clear is that Pakistan's
air defense is is joke. It's it's a
joke. It's
non-existent. Forget about stopping
Abraos. They can't even detect a drone,
a slowmoving loitering
drone. That's how bad the Chinese air
defense systems are. Because these are
Chinese air defense systems. Yeah. And
they have fired air fired Chinese
missiles at us. And apparently a Chinese
missile was found found deep into deep
inside Indian territory. More or less
intact. It apparently did not hit any
target. It just ran out of fuel and
dropped. So it's kind of damaged but not
damaged in the sense that it slammed
into something. It just ran out of fuel
and dropped down. That's it. So that's
um I would say very valuable war booty.
and
our engineers and scientists are now
going to take that thing apart and
they're going to glean out all the
secrets, all the secrets of China's
technology. Maybe the missiles were
better than the air defense systems,
right? At least the missile flew 100 km
into Indian territory before dropping
and not doing anything. But what kind of
seekers does do those missiles have and
what are the electronics like and so on?
That's very interesting to know and I'm
sure the our our American friends will
also be interested in knowing what this
is like. So maybe we can make a trade
you know you give us David Coleman
Headley Headley and we give you the
Chinese missile or something like that.
Um, Bang says, "In the worst case
scenario of a nuclear exchange, are we
capable of intercepting their warheads
without major losses on our
side?"
Probably. Yeah. See they have tried one
thing that's very clear is that the
Pakistanis have tried their best to hit
Indian targets like not towns and
villages but big cities military
installations they've they've lobbed
hundreds of drones and missiles at us
and our air defenses have taken all of
these down no major hits have happened
right so we have been able to take out
drones maybe cruise missiles and be
maybe
rockets. Now when it comes to a nuclear
exchange, a hypothetical scenario which
we don't ever want to see but let's
discuss it. When it comes to a nuclear
exchange, there's two way of delivering
nukes as far as I understand from the
Pakistani side. One is ballistic
missiles. They have all those ugly
sounding ballistic missiles, right? All
those names uh names of Turk invaders,
Gori, Gaznavi and whatnot. So those are
short to medium-range ballistic
missiles. Those have a very predictable
par parabolic trajectory
and once you know it's launched, you
kind of know where it's
going. That's one way of delivering a
nuke for from Pakistan's perspective.
The other way is to send a fighter plane
with a nuclear tipped missile on it. So
even if the fighter plane is taken out,
the missile may be hard to take out in
that sort of scenario.
Now I am pretty sure that the S400 can
take out incoming ballistic missiles and
cruise missiles. The these people have
cruise missiles as well which may be you
know low-flying cruise
missiles. So our air defenses will be
extremely high alert the next couple of
weeks. Um I am sure that we have systems
apart from the S400 that can also do the
job. For example, we have the Priti air
defense system which is a two missile
system. One missile does the
interception exo atmospherically outside
of the earth's atmosphere that is above
100 km from the earth's surface and
there's a second layer which is the
endopheric interception which intercepts
the incoming missile at about uh at
about 40 km height. So it's a two-stage
system. If the first one fails the
second one will come into action that
sort of thing. And then we have point
defense systems which include the the
the the the Akash missile and whatever
else we've been using the past couple of
days. So I think we have pretty good
uh air defense systems which can take
out missiles of various kinds.
Um so I think we we should be in good
shape and uh we will probably have these
systems u uh positioned in strategic
locations in all major
cities. That's what I expect without
actually knowing uh the details. Right?
So I think we should be in good in good
shape and I think we should not worry
too much about this.
Okay. Um, daddy of dudu or di whatever
says when Pakistan breaks up, what
happens to the Pakistani army who
controls the bases in Sindra, Punjab,
Buljasthan, Kyber Pakula? Whose vasals
will they be and who will have boots on
the
ground? Good question. Look, when
Pakistan breaks up, the army needs to
be what's
the politically correct word? It needs
to be
neutralized. Okay. It needs to be um
yeah I I would say it needs to be
neutralized by by India whenever the
breakup happens. Uh no element who was a
member of the armed forces can be
allowed to to roam the world free. They
are all criminals. So they will all have
to be rounded up and processed. And uh
overall this this organization
uh the ISI military terrorism
combination combined entity it needs to
be completely thoroughly defanged and
neutralized in whichever way is
necessary. Well let's not get into the
details those operational details the
armed forces can take care of in their
own way and they know how to do it. So
that needs to happen to the Pakistan
army. Absolutely. Then the question is
who gets to control the bases in
Sindraesh, Punjab, Baljasthan,
Karakuma.
Um eventually these nations once they
become properly independent and stand on
their feet, they can set up their own
things. But I think we should be there
in an advisory uh capacity. India, we
should learn from the way the Bangladesh
situation was happen was handled in
1971. We just handed over Bangladesh to
to a very new and inexperienced
government which was soon taken out by
the military and it became a military
dictatorship. We don't want new military
dictatorships emerging in these four
nations. However, Patun can go back into
Afghanistan and the Taliban government
can take care of it. That's fine. But
Sudesh, Punjab, Baluchasthan should have
proper clean non-military democracies
and no military rule again in the
future. So we need to have a transition
phase of a few years in which we
handhold them through the process of
becoming proper good democracies and all
that. So I think we need to do it not
anybody else and we can't have the
United Nations coming in parachuting in
we we liberate the countries and the UN
comes in then no stay out get out. So uh
we will have to do this whenever this
happens hopefully soon. Uh we don't want
to call them vasals and we should not
treat anyone as vasals. We don't play
the game that way, but we will certainly
be um so to say a mentor or a guide and
overall the civilizational um same
entity, right? That sort of
thing. Okay. Veov says, "Don't trust the
media. I was a practicing anti- media. I
trusted them for once yesterday and they
betrayed me by spreading lies about
Karachi airport and a Pakistani
soldier." Okay. Okay, I don't know which
media network betrayed you. Look, the
Indian media is a
joke. The Indian media is a joke. I
repeat
that. Have you seen the Indian media
coverage of
anything? It's hyperbolic. It's over the
top. I was trying to watch some news
today and half the Indian media channels
who are covering the war have sirens
going on in the background. So there are
like 78 people on the screen trying to
talk at the same time. In the background
there's the sound wailing sound of of
sirens and and and below the the
participants there are flames and and
helicopters and fighter planes flying
around. That's the way they they do
their job. That's that's their coverage
of of of of a war. And even the calmst
channels will have six people minimum on
the screen all talking at the same time.
and their analysis uh it is painful to
watch and there are certain India Indian
media channels on which retired armed
forces people come wearing
uniforms and they will they'll be happy
to say whatever is the most inflammatory
thing and of course you're paid to do
this so they'll play their role and the
I would say the Hindi speaking media is
is the the the level of analysis is like
several notches below the English
speaking media and in the English
speaking
channels there are no real
analysts
h the best analysts they have are news
readers they simply read the news of a
teleprompter they don't have any
analytical
ability so the Indian media is a joke
and then there's a lot of nonsense that
comes out on it okay and uh half of what
they claim during wartime time is is
just
rumors. Some of it may be true but uh as
long as the government doesn't
corroborate it, it it becomes a rumor.
So that sort of thing. My point is
um it it is it is not a good idea to
trust what the media says. Um and some
of the Indian media outlets actually
take the side of the
enemy and it's high time for the
government to block these from being
accessed in India. It's okay for them to
be accessible to Pakistanis but not here
in India. Lot of India's med a lot of
India's media
outlets a significant percentage of
these take the side of India's
enemies. Uh so that's a big problem for
India. So yeah it's it's difficult to
trust the media. It's hard to trust the
media and you should not trust the
media. Uh what I would suggest is that
you should only believe what the
government says.
uh if if you are from the US or if you
are from the west listening to this they
laugh at what we are saying because they
don't trust their governments but at
this time in India you should only
believe what is of what is being said
officially in the daily press
conferences of course they will of not
tell you everything that's happening but
it's a good thing
um geopolitical dub says is there any
possibility of a military coup because
of the pressure of on the army in the
temporary nation again. Oh, it's a big
possibility. Uh if the next few days
Pakistan can't you know land blows on
India, Aim Mun his job is going to be
very tenuous. His his job is going to be
under threat. His life could be under
threat. And the longer this continues
and the longer Pakistan is hit by India
at will and the longer the Pakistanis
are unable to land blows on India, the
higher the pressure will mount on the
Pakistani military leadership. The first
target is going to be Aim Munir. The
first thing that generals will do is
that they're going to put point the
finger of blame at at Aim Munir. He's
going to be out. It may happen in the
next 3 4 days, one week at most. If in
one week's time Pakistan is still being
hammered and is unable to do anything
back at India, aim I can promise you is
going to be gone. But then whoever comes
in his place, the pressure will
immediately fall on that
person. So even a military coup is not
going to solve the problem the Pakistani
military faces. And the problem is that
they are incapable of defeating India
and they're incapable of defending their
country against
India. So that is the conundrum and
that's why if the situation continues in
two weeks time Pakistan is going to
disintegrate maximum two weeks
time. Amisha says Dr. Jash Shankar the
Indian foreign minister says firm
resolute response to terrorism at Europe
day
celebrations. I think the message is
loud and clear. So Dr. Jashankar is
doing exactly what needs to be done. I
was saying yesterday somebody had asked
me what should be done, what should
India do when it comes to messaging to
the world about what's happening and
he's doing exactly what needs to be
done. He's talking to all the top
diplomats in the world, all the foreign
ministers, all the people that matter
and he is constantly conveying India's
position that we are doing the right
thing. We are not a terrorist nation. We
are fighting against terrorism. We are
simply responding to terror and our our
actions are measured and they are
proportionate and we are willing to
deescalate right now as long as the
Pakistanis back down and stand down but
if they escalate we're going to respond
to that. So that message is loud and
clear. It's being re reiterated every
single day which which is what needs to
happen. So good exactly what's needs
what needs to be
done. Okay. Pranay Paul says how
vulnerable are Indian cities in the east
like Gujhati or Kolkata to proxy attacks
or misdirection tactics. Yeah. Uh I kind
of took that question some time ago. The
question from Chuching. Uh every Indian
city whether it's east, west, north,
south is going to have to be on much
higher alert than normal because our
cities are infiltrated by foreigners.
We may have a 100 million Bangladeshes
living in India, right? And we have had
years to take care of the threat, but
how many have been deported? These
people, the the illegal Bangladeshi
infiltrators, the illegal Rohingya
infiltrators, the illegal Pakistani
infiltrators, the illegal cookies, these
people are foreigners. They don't have
any allegiance to Indian culture,
civilization or the Indian nation. They
have no love for us, the Indian people.
They can be used as tools as pawns by
foreign forces to wage war against our
nation from
within. So um and look Pakistan is
finding out very badly that it's unable
to land any military blows on India. So
then they will want to resort to their
standard tactics of terrorism and they
will have sleeper cells within India.
all these foreigners who are sitting in
India and if you want to activate
Rohingya in Bangladesh, the Bangladesh
government will be happy to do it.
Muhammad Inus is an enemy of India and
uh even the cookies may have some
connections with Muhammad or perhaps
China perhaps China or or who knows what
else. So you know big big big problem we
have enemies within and as long as they
exist on our soil we are vulnerable. So
yeah, we we are
uh uh we are at at risk when it comes to
these
matters. Samaruti says uh Pakistani F-16
went down with an Awax aircraft as well
advanced warning ADL combat system or
something it's called with no
confirmation of of Chinese two JF7s
down. What do you think? Also seems like
explosions heard in Samba, Jammu and
Kashmir right now on Samba and Patan Kot
also. Look the action is continuing. The
war is on right now as we speak. I can
see on the TV screen behind me that
Pakistan is apparently widening the
conflict. It it is attacking the west of
India and the north of India right now
as we speak
apparently. And uh what about these
aircraft that have apparently been hit?
One Avax. The Avac would have been
flying over Pakistan territory. uh it
would not be stupid enough to to intrude
into Indian territory but F-16s and J17s
they will come into Indian territory if
they are deployed and if they are doing
that they are sending their pilots to
their
deaths. So even I heard the last 48
hours that uh one F-16 and two JF7s went
down but the Indian government has not
said a word about this. So we we stay
quiet because look the Pakistanis as
long as we don't show the proof the
Pakistanis will try to brush this under
under the carpet that they lost two
aircraft or three aircraft and the
Pakistanis have a history of downoning
their
soldiers. So how about we keep this
quiet? We
don't shot from the rooftops that we
took out three fighter planes. We take
the
pilots and we interrogate them. They
find out everything they have we have to
there is to know from these pilots. And
if we tell the world that we have one
pilot or two pilots who are uh who who
who have been captured then then the
world will start pressure trying to
pressurize India you know be magnanimous
and return the pirate to Pakistan. You
know the Pakistanis gave back Abinandan.
They gave back Abinandan because we said
we're going to fratten your country with
Brahos missiles all over the place.
That's why they gave Abinand back.
So if we have a Pakistani pilot, if we
have, I'm not saying we have, but if we
have a Pakistani pilot, we should not
tell the world about it. Hold him,
squeeze him, interrogate him, be humane.
We don't like Pakistanis who will
torture prisoners, but interrogate the
guy, right? Get out all the valuable
intel and then we'll see what to do
later.
So, so in case we have shot down fighter
planes, maybe that's why we are keeping
it quiet perhaps. But I'm not saying we
have. I'm not saying we have. I'm not
saying we have not. You know, it's all
hypotheticals right now. But I hope you
understand the thought process behind
keeping such a matter quiet if it has
happened.
Okay. Geopolitical Dub again says, "Will
the borders of India, Israel, and Russia
expand in the near future? Is it
inevitable? Russia's borders have
expanded recently. They took Crimea in
2014 and now they've taken since 22
they've taken about roughly roughly a
quarter of Ukraine give or take 1/4 or
1/5if of Ukraine. So their borders have
already changed. Maybe if there's a
ceasefire agreement sometime soon then
the borders will kind of freeze for a
while for Russia. Uh apart from the
Ukraine region, I don't see any Russian
expansion anywhere else in the near
future at least. Uh so that's about
Russia. Israel. Yeah, I think uh their
borders have expanded recently after the
Syria Syria regime change operation and
all that. They've got they have nibbled
away at some parts of Syria and they
have control over more of the territory
in the Golan Heights region and around
that time mount he what I forget the
name of the mountain and so on. So yeah,
Israel's territory has kind of crept uh
forward a little bit. What about India?
I think in the next two weeks the
borders of the subcontinent will
subcontinent may change if Pakistan
collapses. If this war continues the
next two weeks Pakistan will
collapse. That's that's how far actually
that's how close Pakistan is to
collapse. Just two weeks maximum if this
war continues in that case the borders
of India will change they will
expand. Kush Adwani says what news
sources do you follow to know what's
happening live? I look at everything.
I if I decide that okay I want I want to
take stock of what's happening I give
myself 15 minutes 20 minutes maybe half
an hour and I just surf all TV channels
all the news channels uh you go to
YouTube and it's live you go there's
live live streams of all major media
outlets whether it's Indian media
outlets or other media outlets and you
quickly scan what's happening and what
they are saying that's how I do it and
obviously I have online sources as well
that I read so the right approach for me
from my perspective is to have a 360
degree perspective. Uh see what what
Indian channels are saying. See what
Pakistani channels if accessible are
saying. See what the west is saying. See
what the Chinese are saying. See what
the Russians are saying. See what
everybody else is saying. See what the
Arabs are saying. Al Jazza. Get a
360°ree perspective. And I because of uh
my understanding I know what perspective
each media network has. I know what BBC
will say about India. I know what uh
Alzer will say about India. I know what
the New York Times will say. I know what
the Washington Post will say. I know
what Lufigo will say. I know what
Deutsche will say. I know each channel
has a specific approach towards India
and the matters of the subcontinent. So
if they are saying this, what does it
really mean? I kind of can tell, you
know, I it's it's something you develop
over time with experience. So that's
what I do and then I get a proper
perspective and then I draw my own
conclusions based on very specific data
points, hard data points which is
typically numbers, which is typically
based on numbers. So you can actually
you know uh foresee scenarios and assign
percentages to each scenario and that
sort of thing a forecasting methodology
which involves a bit of statistical
analysis and predictive analysis. So
that's kind of how I do
things.
Okay. Tushar says Tushar Kalborgi says
has a coup against the Pakistani chief
as Munir. I don't see any such thing
having happened thus far.
Now this is an interesting point by
Jotish Sharma. We could see Pakistan
sending civilian aircraft right now
hiding behind civilian aircraft while
attacking. What steps could be done?
Let's take a look at this shall
we? Give me a second. I'll put this on
the screen. I usually have a map on the
screen. This time I'm going to have a
different kind of a map on the screen.
Give me a second.
And this is a live
view of uh air activity in the world.
This is called flight radar 24. It's a
it's a very good resource to
to that you can use to see what's
happening. So as always, you're going to
have a big hole in the sky. Nothing
flying over Ukraine for obvious reasons.
Nobody wants to fly over Ukraine right
now. And now over Pakistan, you have a
couple of aircraft
So as you can see we have a whole bunch
of aircraft in Delhi but we have shut
off the airspace north of Delhi. So so
there's no aircraft going to Lei,
there's no aircraft going into Punjab,
no aircraft going to Chandigar, no
aircraft aircraft going into Shirinagar
and so on. Rajasthan also seems to be
right now um quiet but in Pakistan there
are aircraft flying. What is this? This
is a Pakistan International Airlines
aircraft from Karachi to
Lahore. Now you have more aircraft. This
is what this is Islamabad the Dam. What
is this here? Karach to Islamabad and so
on. So they are still operating
commercial aircraft at a time when they
are at war and they are trying to hit
Indian uh targets with drones and
missiles and rockets and they know that
India is going to fight fire back at
them. So what the Pakistanis want let me
explain to you. Okay. Okay. What the
Pakistanis want? They want India to
mistakenly target a civilian aircraft so
that they get to cry victim. They get to
play victim. If India makes a mistake
and by mistake takes down a civilian
aircraft which can happen during a time
of war, then Pakistan gets to play
victim. That's what they're trying to
do. They have their own civilians who
are flying in these commercial planes
and they are using these civilians as
shields. These look just imagine what
kind of mindset the Pakistani government
military ISI terrorism complex has a
criminal mindset. They are hiding behind
their own civilians. They're using their
own civilians as shields and they want
India to shoot down one of these
commercial aircraft. If that happens,
they can they can go to the world and
say that India is is evil and we are the
victims and we are the and India is the
aggressor. That's what they are trying
to do. Shameful people. They want this
to happen. They want their people to
die. They want India to make a mistake
and shoot down a civilian
aircraft. Abysmal, horrible, horrible
approach the Pakistanis have. Uh, okay.
What else do we have? Luffy says,
"India's military vastly outmatches
Pakistan's. Yet history shows that
weaker powers like Vietnam and
Afghanistan have defeated stronger
adversaries. Can Pakistan ever dream of
doing the same. So Vietnam defeated the
United States. The United States came
from half the planet away. And the
Vietnamese knew how to fight on their
own land, right? And they knew that land
very well. and they were fighting for
their homeland. So they were much more
motivated than the Americans who were
who had come from god knows where and
who had who half of them did they don't
even know what they were fighting for.
That's why the Vietnamese were able to
win at tremendous cost to their country.
They're still paying the price. There
are still bombs all over Vietnam.
Horrible. What about Afghanistan?
Afghanistan was invaded by the Soviets.
The Soviet Union is far away. The
Russians Russia is far away from
Afghanistan, right? So the Afghans, the
Pashons were defending their homeland.
They had nowhere else to go. So they
were they fought and that's why they won
and they understood their territory
better than the Russians. That's why
they fought. Now when it comes to fight
between India and Pakistan,
um Pakistan is historically our
territory. It was given away by people
against who did not consult India. So we
know the territory like the back of our
hand. It is our territory and we are not
foreign
invaders. So you you see there's a big
difference big huge difference and we
are not going to kill the Pakistanis and
steal their land. We're going to
liberate them from the oppressor which
is the Pakistani military ISI terrorism
complex. So we are not foreign invaders.
We're going to be liberators and our
power does vastly outmatch Pakistan and
all that. So you have to pick the right
examples. Giving the example of Vietnam
against the US or Afghanistan against
the USSR is not the right example. It's
not the right comparison to make. In our
case of Pakistan is our territory
historically. We know it really well. We
know the people. We know the culture. We
know everything. And we're fighting a
just war here. We are the victims and we
want to liberate the people of Pakistan
from the oppressor and we don't want to
steal their resources and their
territory and what not. We just want to
end the reign of terror of the Pakistani
ISI military complex and then be done
with it. Big big big difference huge
difference. Okay. Surendra Gupta says
the S400 proves to be a sophisticated
air defense system. What are the other
air defense systems being used by India?
The S400 is hardly being used. Okay, the
don't don't listen to the media. The
media has no idea what's happening. The
S400, like I said in the beginning of
today's live stream, the S400 is used
for very specific cases. It is used to
take out fighter planes. It's used to
take out ballistic missiles and possibly
cruise missiles. It's not used to take
out drones and rockets and artillery
shells and whatnot. No, that for doing
that we have other systems. And the
system that has turned out to be the
superstar in the past 48 hours is the
Akash SAM, the Akash surfaceto-air
missile that's turned out to be the real
superhero in the past 48 hours. So it's
the Akash SAM that has been the the
hero, the star of the action the past
40,000 and right now as well the S400
it's used for bigger
threats like F-16s like JF17 fighter
planes made by China or ballistic
missiles and so on short to medium range
and so on.
Okay, Dave says how long are we going to
play defense? I think it's high time we
should make the first move rather than
waiting for Pakistan to make the move.
What are your thoughts on
[Music]
this?
Patience. And I'm not saying be patient
the next 10 years. I'm saying
wait one to two
weeks. See, let's understand what's
happening. I I understand. I I see um I
see journalists on Twitter saying how I
I don't understand India's
restraint. A journalist tweeted that
yesterday. Understand what's happening.
The Pakistanis for better or for worse,
for good or for bad have given India a
once in 80 years opportunity to end the
terror state once and for
all. Okay. Pakistan is running short of
supplies.
They as a vasal of the Biden regime,
they gave a lot of ammunition to
Ukraine. Now they are running short of
ammunition.
They are trying to lob missiles and
rockets and drones at us right now. It's
happening right now. Last night they
fired they they they lobbed more than
400 to 500 drones, Turkish drones at us.
Nothing was hit. Everything was taken
out and we have been hitting them at
will. We did it very
visibly. The Pakistanis can't deny what
we've destroyed. the terror
infrastructure, the headquarters of the
the lashkar toba, the cricket stadium in
raindi, the air defense system in Lahore
and something in Karachi and whatn not
we have hit them visibly in broad
daylight at will. So what is the
perception that the Pakistani public
will have? The military is incompetent.
Incompetent. They can't defend the
country. They can't defend themselves
and they can't hit India even though
they've been trying the past 14 hours.
The longer this situation
continues, the more pressure there will
be on the military. And the more the
fault lines within Pakistan will become
active. Balojasthan is already declaring
independence. Sindra will become
restive. the khibar pakun who are the
puns they'll say enough we don't want
the Pakistani military above us we are
going back to Afghanistan they'll rise
up and revolt against the Pakistani
military and soon you'll have revolts
all over the country the longer this
lasts the more precarious the situation
of the Pakistani military uh
dictatorship become
becomes all we have to do see if the
Pakistanis failed to hit a big target in
India then it means the military is is
an illegitimate force and this they've
been trying 48 hours they'll try tonight
won't work they'll try it next 3 4 days
by the time the public pressure will be
too high and you'll have riots on the
streets so the Pakistani military is
facing a clicking a ticking clock a
countdown to
zero two weeks at most before Pakistan
disintegrates two weeks at most before
Pakistan disintegrates so we don't have
to Play offense. Play defense. Make sure
Pakistan can't hit you. They keep trying
to hit you. Don't allow them. And when
the time is right, you make your
move. And the time is going to be right
within the next 2
weeks. Wait. Have a little patience. We
have waited how many years? Almost 80
years.
Wait. It's going to take two to 14 days.
2 to 14 days if the situation continues.
Unless the Indian government says okay,
we will genuinely
disengage which I don't think Mr. Modi
wants to do knowing Mr.
Modi. Mr.
Modi, Mr. Modi is a different kind of
prime minister. I don't think he will
let go of this opportunity. And the
Americans are uh have made it very clear
that as long as the situation doesn't
spill beyond the Indian
subcontinent, we can do what we
want. I think we are living in a
historic time. We are witnessing um a
turning point in world history. The
beginning of the turning point. So
patience,
patience. All right.
Um same question. Will Pakistan learn a
lesson or continue terrorism in the
future? They won't last more than two
weeks the way things are going. So
there's no lesson to be learned. It's
over. Pakistan won't exist possibly in
two weeks.
And I hope I am
right. Okay.
Um, Mr. 88 says, "Is there any chance
the US may impose sanctions on us if the
war drags on as the Indian government
consider the threat the threat of
potential US tariffs? We are currently
in the process of
negotiating the the tariff issue with
the US right
now. Right now as we speak, we may be in
the final phases of the negotiations. So
we are doing exactly what the Americans
want when it comes to the
tariffs. So so there is nothing um there
is no point of contention there. When it
comes to
sanctions, why would they sanction a
nation that they need on their side?
They need on to be on the side in the
effort to contain China. We are in the
beginning of a of a new cold war. The US
versus China and they need India on
their side. India is a vital piece of
the puzzle for them. It's the only
nation in Eurasia that can stand up to
China. Russia can, but Russia is on
China's side right now because Russia
has no
choice. So in the US needs India on its
side. Why why would they impose
sanctions on India?
You would do that only if you're
suicidal, right? There is no chance the
US will impose sanctions on India. And
if you go by the what what JD Vance, the
vice president of the US said yesterday,
he essentially gave the message that
India can do what it wants with Pakistan
as long as the situation does not spill
out of beyond the Indian subcontinent.
Deal with them, do whatever you want,
but be on our side when it comes to
China. Right.
Um let's see what else do we have. Um
we're going to talk about the Pakistan
issue today. There are all kinds of
other questions but right now is not the
time for the other
questions.
Um geopolitical dubas is India waiting.
Now this is a good question. Is India
waiting for Pakistan to use up all their
drones, all their missiles? Yeah. Then
they will come they will charge at us on
horses and donkeys. See Pakistan has a
limited supply of drones, missiles,
whatso whatever. They may have some
factories that that make bullets and
shells perhaps but the sophisticated
weaponry like drones, missiles and
whatnot, it comes from beyond Pakistan.
Uh some of it is supplied by China, some
of it by Turkey. The drones they used
yesterday, 400, 500 drones, they were
these were Turkish drones all failed. So
yeah, let's wait.
Let's wait. Let them try. Let them try.
It's happening right now. They're
they're firing more drones. Apparently,
there are blasts in Kurtarpur and so on.
They are trying. The Pakistanis are
trying. Keep
trying. We have adequate supplies of
everything we need. We have our own
factories that make the the drones and
ammunition and
whatnot. So, just wait patiently next 3
4 days, one week. In one week, they'll
have nothing left.
So yeah, you're right. It's a wait and
watch strategy right now. Right now, let
them use up everything they have. Then
we'll deal with
them. Divan Shu says, "Uh, does this
Indopak war have anything have any
connection or relation to the Bangladesh
uprising? Like can we link this war to
the uprisings in Bangladesh? Are there
uprisings in Bangladesh right now? I am
not aware of. If there are uprisings
happening in Bangladesh right now, I'm
not aware of them. We recently had a
regime change in Bangladesh. Is that
what you're referring to? In which
Shazina was ousted and uh Muhammad Yinus
was was brought to power by the
Americans. That was the Biden regime.
Trump doesn't seem to have any fondness
for the Biden regime u installed
government in Bangladesh. But they may
use it for something. Maybe they want to
have an air base or some kind of
military base in Bangladesh. In which
case Bangladesh will be useful to them,
useful for them. But I don't think the
Indopac war that's happening right now
is connected to Bangladesh. If
Bangladesh if Bangladesh becomes active
militarily then there there may be a
connection. But right now this is simply
Pakistan's own doing this is simply
their own stupidity that has brought
them in this in this position of being
caught between a rock and a hard place
with nowhere to go. Here here both bad.
That's where they are right now. So this
is a problem that they find themselves
in and it's a problem of their own
making. They made this. They have dug
their
grave. Kick says, "Isn't it dangerous to
engage in a long war when there's more
than 100 million illegal infiltrators
again inside India? Now Pakistani agents
can easily enter India via East
Pakistan. That's the one Achilles heel
of India. And I I simply don't
understand why the government has not
evicted these illegals the past 10 11
years. I just don't get
it. So that is a problem. Now I hope
that this
war serves as an inflection point as a
turning point as a tipping point for
India and going forward we adopt a
complete non-tolerance policy towards
illegal infiltrators. Recently we uh
deported tens of thousands of illegal
Pakistani infiltrators who had been
living in India. Some of them for
decades. Some of them even have
generations of of kids living in India.
All of them have to be
deported. Just because you born in India
doesn't make you Indian. Do you
understand that? That's India's policy.
That's India's law. We don't recognize
citizenship by birth.
We don't recognize
Yusuli. We recognize Yus Sanguinis
citizenship by
descent. So if you are a Bangladeshi who
infiltrated into India in 1971 and that
Bangladeshi has children and
grandchildren, they should all be
deported. You cannot be soft-hearted in
matters of national security when it
comes to people who have no allegiance
to you or your nation or your culture or
your civilization.
They have to be all deported. It's not
my fault that they were born here.
Right? It's not our country's fault that
they were born here. They came in
illegally. They have to go out. The same
applies to Rohingya, to Bangladesh, to
Pakistanis, to cookies, everybody out. I
hope the government adopts a
non-tolerance policy going forward
because it is a national security
threat. It is a huge drain on our
economy. Imagine a 100 million people
leeching of your economy, of your
resources. It's high time the government
does something about this. Let this be
hopefully um a tipping point, a turning
point for India. I hope
so. Tanmay Desh Pand says, I heard that
tonight's IMF meeting, International
Monetary Fund meeting will decide the
future of the war of this war. If the
Pakistanis are given a loan, then India
will not back down. What are my
thoughts? Because they attacked Jammu
right now. Who is the IMF to decide the
future of this war or the future of what
happens in our
subcontinent? Who the hell are the IMF
to decide
that? And if they give a loan to
Pakistan, they are simply funding and
financing
terrorism. I think it will make sense
for them not to do it. But if they do,
well
then we we should do what we have to do.
And we have Pakistan where Pakistan
deserves to be right now. Caught between
a rock and a hard place. Caught between
the devil and the deep
sea. So now that we have Pakistan where
we want
them, we should take this to the end
game and finish this off. When there's
no Pakistan left, what will the IMF do?
Who will they give that money to? It's a
matter of one or two
weeks. Yeah. So, Pakistan will be
attacking right now. I don't know.
They're attacking Jammu. Are they
possibly? I have a TV screen in front of
me on the other side of the lens. So,
behind the
lens, right? And the same question I get
every time. Space Ed says, "Is this is
the best chance to capture PK? It'll
affect both Pakistan and China. Why is
India not taking advantage of the
situation?" I answered the question just
now like 5 minutes ago. This is not the
best chance to to capture P. This is the
best chance to dismantle Pakistan. This
is bigger than P. This is free Balo.
This is this is the independence of
Balojasthan. This is the independence of
Sinduh. This is the reintegration of
Kaibar Pakuna into Afghanistan and the
reintegration of Gilgit Baltistan and
Pakistan occupied Kashmir into India.
That's what we are staring at right
now. That's where we are. It's not about
P anymore. It's about the future of
Pakistan itself. Pakistan has reached
that stage right now that in two weeks
there would there can be no there
possibly will be no Pakistan left.
That's where we are. Nutan says what
about project K? It's not about
Pakistan. But yeah, what about project
K? I think it all depends on the Trump
regime because project K cookie land for
Christ. this project of creating a fake
artificial Pakistan-like country out of
parts of India, Bangladesh,
uh Myanmar and the Indian states of
Manipur and uh Misoram. That project
cookie land for Christ project K is a US
creation. It was a creation of the Biden
regime which was very bitterly
anti-India.
Now Trump seems to have a different
policy towards India. He needs India on
on his side when it comes to the China
matter. I think it is time for Trump and
his regime, his
administration to to
end the funding and the support for
project K and whatever other uh
nefarious activities the Americans have
been um conducting in India's far east
which in includes Misoram, Manipur,
Nagaland and whatnot, Arunachala Pradesh
as well. the industrial scale
Christianization project that has been
going on for a long time all of that
needs to end if they need us if they
want us on their side so project K needs
to be dismantled and once that happens
India should take the same kind of
action in Manipur and Mizuram that's
what's happening right now on the
western border and evict all the
foreigners squatting on Indian territory
and and um you know brutalizing the
natives the indigenous Indians that
needs to happen so I think that's the
next phase once Once we deal with
Pakistan, we need to deal with
that. Right. Okay. Let's see some more
questions.
Um, Yubra Shikawad says, "Why are you
saying cookies are outsiders? Some of
them are in India, some are in
Bangladesh, some are in Myanmar. So, we
have some culture link. Why? So, why we
join them in India instead of breaking
India?" Sir, you have absolutely no
understanding of the history, right?
You only see the perspective of you take
a picture of the world like this as it
is right now and you say oh there are
these people here so why are you seeing
the outsiders learn some history study
some history take some time take some
time spend some energy I know studying
is hard and difficult it hurts the mind
if you don't know your history you will
never know what's going to happen to
your country you will have no control
over what's
happening the cookies are foreigners
they were brought in by the British
as a punishment to the locals. Please
learn history before talking nonsense
sir. Otherwise you'll say even
Bangladeshes are insiders. Why are you
saying we should remove
Bangladeshes? If you don't know history,
you should spend some time to study it
before making silly
statements. Okay? No foreigners should
be in India, especially those who act
like barbarians.
and who kill innocent people. You have
no idea of what they've been doing in
Manipur even in the past 3 years, two
years, right? Since May 23 and you have
no idea of their history before May
23, they have been fighting the
Bangladeshes to create a separate
country. They in the 1990s they fought
the Nagal Nagas of Nagaland and
Manipur. They tried to kill them all.
Since the 19th century, they have been
killing locals, indigenous people. You
have no understanding but you want to
pass judgment over what should be. I
just don't get
Indians. I I know it's not your fault.
You you are taught nothing in the
education system. The education system
doesn't teach real history. But you have
a responsibility to learn it on your
own. If your school teacher did not
teach you or if your textbook did not
teach you, learn some history.
Otherwise, you will be a person who is
rudderless and you know you will support
the wrong causes and that's not good for
your country, is it?
Radha says if Pakistan breaks up into
pieces will terrorism die with it or
will it take some new form? See
terrorism terrorism needs funding.
Terrorism needs a certain
um support. It also needs fertile ground
ideologically, culturally etc.
So it is
um to end terrorism you have to first of
all end funding for terrorism and you
also have to end the terrorists the
people who have indulged in terrorism in
the past you have
to neutralize them eliminate them in
whichever form you want to. So it it's
it's not going to be easy even after
Pakistan breaks up to completely stamp
out terrorism. It's going to be a
process. It'll take some time. The first
thing you have to do is to dradicalize
the population which generally takes 30
40 50 60 years. How did Pakistan get
radicalized and become a terrorist
nation? Started in the 1980s with the
reforms in the education system
implemented by Za Hak the military
dictator of Pakistan who hanged
Zulfikiar Ali Bhut. That guy reformed
his education system and completely
radicalized his people as as a result.
And which is why I keep saying we need
to reform our education system so as to
you know have a higher quality
population. Our education system is
keeping our people illiterate and people
then ask questions like why do you
consider cookies outsiders or Bangladesh
is outsiders because you don't learn
your history. You don't learn what the
national interest is.
So uh coming back to Pakistan, if
Pakistan breaks into pieces, it's going
to be a long process of ending terrorism
because look, the nation may break into
four pieces, but the population is still
the
same. So it's going to be a long road
ahead. It's going to be long road ahead.
It it's just simply breaking Pakistan
into pieces is not going to be the end
of the story. We're going to have to
identify all the terrorists. You can't
allow them to reintegrate into into the
population and claim to be nice people.
The people who have been done doing all
those things, things that that are
unspeakable. You can't have them
reintegrate into society. You have to
permanently remove them from from
society. It's going to be a long
process. But the first step is the
dismantling dismantle disintegration of
Pakistan.
Surita says, "Do you think it's time for
a change in our nuclear doctrine to
first
use okay to have a stated no first use
doctrine and then when if the situation
arises you can do whatever you want.
It's not like we have signed a contract
that we are bound to uh abide by, right?
Um it's I I personally am not in favor
of a no first use doctrine. I personally
believe that every nation should has the
right to use arms that it has either as
first use or second
use. We we are not under any obligation
to not
use any weapon
first. But uh as far as the doctrine is
concerned maybe we can change it but
there's no need to announce it. So we
should keep some ambiguity in my opinion
when it comes to our nuclear doctrine.
Maybe it's okay to make the world
believe that we have a no first use
doctrine but when it suits our national
interest if required we can use it
first. So strategic ambiguity is always
the best way to go about things. But
yeah I agree with you. I don't agree I I
am not in favor of a no first use
doctrine an actual no first use
doctrine. It's it's
silly. And the same question was asked
by Moonlight Sonata. I answered that
question. Okay.
Um Ashwin says why Turkey has this
fondness which is increasing towards
Pakistan. Is it because of hedgemony
towards the Islamic world? If not Saudi
Arabia, we would we would new world
order. Okay. Um I'm kind of getting what
you're asking. Why does Turkey love
Pakistan so much? And what about the
Islamic world? Who wants to be the
leader of the Islamic world? There are s
multiple contenders for the leadership
of the Islamic world. Pakistan says that
we are the only Islamic nuclear power.
We have the Islamic nuclear bomb. So we
should be the leader of the Islamic
world. But they are a rag tag third
world half- naked nation half starving
half bankrupt. So because of that they
they aren't in a position to be the
leaders of the Islamic world. Which
other contenders do we have? Saudi
Arabia is the home of Islam. They they
are the custodians of the great
uh the holiest cities of Islam, right?
Saudi Arabia and they are the richest of
the Islamic nations and they are the
birthplace of the prophet of Islam. So
that makes Saudi Arabia the natural
contender for being the the the leader
of the Islamic world.
Then there's another country called
Turkey and they were the uh they they
are the continuation so to say in a
smaller form of the Ottoman Empire. Uh
the last califf was Turkish. There the
whole institution of the caliphate from
1456 onwards until 192021 around that
time the caliphate lasted. It was all
the califfs were Turks until that in
during that time period. So uh they
consider themselves to be the um natural
contenders for being the leaders of the
Islamic world. And the Saudis and the
Turks don't get along. So there's that
friction there. And then there's one
more contender which is Iran, the
Persian Empire. But the Persian Empire
was not Islamic, right? But uh Iran also
has um these imperial ambitions because
they used to be an empire in the past.
Uh but they are a different kind of
Islamic nation. Half their population
probably doesn't practice Islam anymore.
Um, Islam is not their
ancestral
religion. Um, it's kind of a situation
like India actually, but India never got
converted fully like like Iran did. And
Iran practices Shia Islam which is at
loggerheads with all other forms of all
the other nations which we mentioned
which practice Sunni Islam. So there's
that Islamic schism, right? The Shia
Sunni schism and all that. So that's the
situation when it comes to the
leadership of the Islamic world. So
there's no clear leader right now.
probably the clearest contender is Saudi
Arabia at this point in time and so on.
So why does Turkey have this fondness
for Pakistan? I discussed this some time
ago. Um because they are very similar
nations. Both nations don't have a
history. They have a criminal record and
u Turkey um knows that Pakistan doesn't
really have the the credentials for
being the leader of the Islamic world.
And they also know that the Pakistanis
worship Turkey these days like they used
to worship the Arabs in the past. Um and
they imagine the Pakistanis that they
are descendants of Turks who ruled over
the subcontinent and so on. So Turkey
kind of leverages that and they
hopefully want to uh tap into some of
the nuclear technology in the future if
if possible and so on. Um and there is
this common shared hatred for polytheism
which is us. So that is another you know
factor that causes this convergence
especially when it comes to India
um and so on. So these are the reasons
why Pakistan and Turkey have this
convergence. Okay.
Um so says will a nuclear war happen? No
it won't happen. Don't
worry. Why are the attacks from Pakistan
to Indian cities made in the night?
because it's harder to defend in the
night. Traditionally, it's dark. So,
it's it's harder. There's a little extra
amount of of of difficulty. Maybe look,
in today's day and age, it doesn't
matter whether it's day or night. Your
instruments will tell you everything.
Your technology will be able to shoot
down things in complete total darkness
if you need to. But it it adds a little
extra layer of difficulty. That's why
you typically do things in the middle of
the night like 2:00 a.m. or if you want
to invade a neighboring country, you do
you do the first attack at 5:00 a.m. or
something or 4:00 a.m. before anyone
wakes up the you know the deepest time
of sleep and all that. So that's why
generally it's done in the in the dead
of night. So once darkness falls they
start their their nefarious activity and
that's I believe what's happening right
now in Jammu. Air raid sirens in
Jammu.
Okay. Ruvid says why is the world's
media not covering this war India
Pakistan like the Israel Hamas war or
the Russia Ukraine war you see it's
because the west seems to believe that
their problems are the world's problems
but the world's problems are not their
problems they think that the world is
centered around
them and the things that they are
obsessed with they will cover 24 by7
Israel Hamas it's not even a it's not
even
contest. Hamas is no match for Israel.
But they will cover it
constantly because they are obsessed
with Israel because Israel has a hold
over the
West. Yeah, Israel does have a hold over
the West. So that's why they are
obsessed with that particular conflict,
Israel Hamas War. Every single media uh
every single media outlet will cover it
half the time, half the day, the Israel
Hamas war. But this war India, Pakistan,
no one's talking about it outside of
India, outside of the
subcontinent. So it's because they have
this they they have this delusional view
of the world that the their problems are
the world's problems. Their obsessions
should be the world's obsessions while
the world's problems don't matter to
them. And that situation is changing
because the world is changing. And in a
in a couple of decades, Europe is going
to be the backwater of the world.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, King Doop is saying Pakistan is
doing exactly what Hamas did. They're
trying to create a narrative and they're
trying to play victim and they're trying
to paint India as the villain,
especially on Tik Tok. How should we
tackle this and win the narrative
war? So, we have a population of 1.4
billion people. We are also all over
social media. take some time out every
day to remind the world that this is a
nation that created the Taliban. This is
the nation that sheltered Osama bin
Laden for a decade. This is the nation
that produced people who flew aircraft
into the World Trade Center buildings in
New York City. This is a nation that
produced people who hijack aircraft uh
like the like like the Indian Airlines
aircraft uh IC7 whatever it was. This is
a nation that produced people that
carried out the Mumbai terror attack
Ajal Kasab and so on. This is the nation
that produced people who cut off the
head of the American Jewish journalist
Daniel Pearl and so on. Remind the world
constantly of these facts. Start with
the Osama bin Laden fact. Yes, Pakistan
is a very peaceful country says Osama. I
lived peacefully there for a
decade. Remind the world every day every
Indian can be a warrior on social media
for the cause of the motherland. Right?
If all Indians spend like each if each
Indian spends just 5 minutes a day doing
this, imagine what happens to Pakistani
propaganda. Don't fight Pakistanis. Just
put out facts every day. remind the
world once a day each Indian that
Pakistan is the nation that sheltered
Osama bin Laden and created the
Taliban and killed Daniel Pearl and
whatnot. Okay, you do that the
propaganda will be destroyed. Okay,
that's how you tackle this and win the
narrative war. That what that's what
each citizen can do for India. What the
government needs to do is to win this
war.
Okay. Okay.
Sam Raman says Pakistan is Pakistan
sending swarms of low coast drones to
Jammu Patango Jamir to deplete our air
defense before launching missiles. Using
S400s for cheap drones is super costly.
J Hind we are not using S400s for cheap
drones. We have a multi-layered air
defense
system. Some of these drones we are
bringing them down using non-kinetic
means without hitting them with
anything. Sounds like black magic. Maybe
it is black magic. There are ways of
doing it. Many of these drones are being
brought down
untouched.
Okay. And some of them we are taking
them out with Akash surfaceto-air
missiles. The Akash surfaceto-air
missile we have in very large quantities
and we make it at home. We don't import
it from somewhere. So Mr. Modi will say,
"Okay, call up. I need 10,000 more. Can
I have them in a week's time?" What? You
know that's how it is. So we are not
going to run out of anything. Our air
defenses won't be depleted. We also have
other air defense systems which I will
not name here. The S400 is not being
used for cheap drones. It's hardly been
used. It has allegedly been used three
times only thus
far to allegedly perhaps bring down
something larger. The S400 is for larger
targets. It's not for drones, cheap
drones. All right. So don't worry we are
covered we we are well
prepared.
Mur Muri Krishna says what's the
advantage of having a cricket stadium? I
I think you'll have to ask somebody else
maybe in the armed forces why did you
choose the cricket stadium in Ral Pendi?
Look first of all it uh did not kill any
civilian.
Um I I don't know. I I I would I will
choose not to speculate about why we
hate a cricket
stadium, but yeah. So apparently the
there's some Pakistani version of the
IPL that exists apparently and uh it's
called the Pakistan Super League or PSL
or something and some lowquality
cricketers play there apparently who
can't play the IPL were not good enough
to play the IPL. So apparently that
Pakistan league is happening and we hit
the stadium and now the Pakistanis have
decided
to possibly take the league out of
Pakistan maybe play in the UAE but
apparently the UAE's cricket board has
said that we you are not welcome here.
So I'm not sure where they will play
now. Maldives, Bangladesh, not
sure whatever. Apparently even the IPL
our IPL has been postponed by a week or
something. So yeah, that's uh what
happens when you're at war.
Okay. Okay. I've already taken the
nuclear doctrine question. So, let's
take some other questions. Um
uh let us see. Let us see. Okay. This is
a good question.
Daksha G says, "Will the Indian economy
have an impact? Will there be an impact
on the Indian economy? Do you think
Bajjasthan might get liberated if this
war lasts for more than 10
days? Do you think it's the end of the
temporary nation?
If this war lasts 14 days, it's the end
of the temporal edition. Pakistan is
less than two weeks away from collapse.
If it doesn't stop what it's doing and
it is in no position to stop what it's
doing. So I think we are staring at the
end of Pakistan in within the next two
weeks. Will there be an impact on the
Indian economy? If the war lasts 3
months, there could be an impact. But if
it ends within two weeks, it's
over. It's completely over and there
won't be any more Pakistan. So yes,
Balojasthan might get liberated in the
next 14 days maximum. Pakistan may cease
to exist in the next 14 days and once
that exists there is no question of
instability in India. So the economy is
completely fine. But if the war lasts
long and drags on like what happened in
Ukraine, there could be an impact the
Indian economy. So Mr. Modi will ensure
it doesn't go in that direction.
Whatever happens will be over in the
next 2 to 14 days.
Okay, let's take some more questions.
Today I'm going to extend this session.
It's already 2 hours 18 minutes.
I'll take it further for today. I'll end
at the time I usually end the live
stream on regular
days. A potato praiser says there's a
two-month night curfew near India
Bangladesh border on our side. Is it? Is
Bangladesh cooking something? I am not
aware of this. This is news to me. I've
not uh I've not heard of this before. Um
so yeah, in case it's true, then maybe
we are taking precautions because
Bangladesh is no longer a friendly
nation, right? After the uh regime
change, there was done recently. So
yeah.
Um Tanesh Pande says our navy is very
strong compared to 1971. We're the sixth
strongest navy in the world and they are
not the Pakistanis are not even in the
top 20. If we do attack Karachi port, it
will be a one-sided affair. I think do
do you also think that I think if we
attack Karachi port Karachi will be
flattened so it's up to us whether do we
do it or not and we don't have to go to
Karachi to do it that's the thing we can
do it from way far away from Karachi we
can do it from 500 km away from
Karachi and we can completely flatten
Karachi if we want so if we attack
Karachi port if we do decide to do it it
will be a completely one-sided affair
Pakistan won't stand a chance Karachi
won't stand a chance the question is do
If you want to do it, if you want to
take the enemy out, you can do it
without destroying the enemy. Look, our
enemy is not the Pakistani people,
right? They hate us. We know that. Most
of them, not all. Most of them hate us.
But uh look, we don't want to attack
civilians. Uh as far as possible, if you
want to take a country, you take it as
intact as
possible. So I don't think this is the
time to attack Karachi port. And if we
do that, then our enemies can paint us
as as cruel people, as aggressors. and
and we don't want that. So maybe not not
a good time to do that to
Pakistan to Karachi. Uh Ainand Ainand
Sen says uh if you were the Pakistani
prime minister, what step would you
realistically take to bring peace to
your people, would you further escalate
or initiate diplomatic discussions with
India? If I was the prime minister of
Pakistan, I would beg the military to
talk to India and stop the war. Because
if I'm the prime minister of Pakistan, I
don't have any power. Please understand
this first of all my dear viewers. The
Pakistani prime minister is a powerless
entity. The Pakistani prime minister
does not decide what happens to his
country or her country. Only one female
minis. So the Pakistani prime minister
is a puppet just like Muhammad
Yunus. Their their rule is to divert
attention from where the real power
lies. It is to make big noises and be
visible while the real power the
military does whatever it wants in the
background. That's the deal. So if I am
the prime minister of Pakistan, I have
no power. There's nothing I can do. If I
was the dictator of Pakistan, if I was
aim, what would I do realistically? I
would immediately seize and stop what I
am doing. I would beg for forgiveness of
the people of Pakistan. I would
dismantle the terror
factories. If Pakistan wants realistic
peace with India, the first thing they
have to do is to dismantle the terrorism
factories and to bring all the
terrorists to justice to hand over the
terrorists that have done per
perpetrated massacres on Indians. Zaki
Rahman Lakmi um um these names are very
strange. Dawud Ibrahim and what what
other names do we have? Um Masoud, Masud
Azar and so on. These individuals have
to be handed over to India. I'm sure I'm
missing a few names. Um but yeah, that's
what Pakistan needs to do. Dismantle the
terror factory. Dismantle the terror
network. Bring all the terrorists to
justice. Hand over the wanted terrorists
to
India. Step down from the role of
dictator. Let there be a genuine
democracy in Pakistan. In that case, I
have no issue with the existence of
Pakistan the way it is. You know, stop
oppressing the people of
Balojasthan. Let the people of Kar
Pakuno go back to Afghanistan. Give P
back to
India. You you do these things then
there's no issue between India and
Pakistan. Give up terrorism as a state
policy. But they can't do it. So that's
why they have that's why they are in the
position they are today.
DIC Shrian says, "Do you think somebody
will bail out Pakistan at the end?" Like
it has happened multiple times in the
past. Now that's a good question. The
first questions we question we have to
ask ourselves is this. Which nations are
potentially in a
position to be able to bail out
Pakistan? Which nations have the
capability to bail out Pakistan from the
position it is in right now? Right now P
Pakistan is in a terrible
position. Okay. It's it's it's India has
a choke hold on Pakistan right now. In
MMA you have a choke hold a rear naked
choke. You're done. That's the position
Pakistan is in right now. So first of
all the question is which
nations can realistically extricate
Pakistan from this position? One nation
that immediately comes to mind is the
US. They can prevent Pakistan from being
destroyed right now if they want
to. They can step in. They can force
India to stop if they want the
Americans. But what did JD Vance say
yesterday? The vice president of the US,
he said this is none of our business.
The IndiaPakistan war, it's none of our
business and we need to stay out of it.
He has made it very clear the Americans
will not intervene this time. It
essentially is a green light to India.
Deal with Pakistan. do whatever you want
finish it off just ensure the matter
doesn't spill beyond the Indian
subcontinent that's it that is a green
light to India this is the chance we
have been waiting for so America is not
going to step in who else can step in
who else exists that is strong enough to
step in
China now is China in a position where
they can force India to stop from what
we are doing let's say we are about to
dismantle Pakistan into four pieces
Are the Chinese in a position to force
us? The Americans can force us through
economic means by just threatening
sanctions if they want, but they don't
want to do it and they're not going to
do it. Can the Chinese impose sanctions
on India? I don't think so. The only
thing the Chinese can threaten India
with is military
action. Now, is China in a position to
start military action with a nation like
India? We are not as powerful as China.
China is three and a half times more
powerful than us. But China is under
siege from the US right now. And the
Americans are waiting for China to make
a stupid move somewhere. If China starts
military action against India, it'll be
a huge mistake for them. The Americans
are waiting for a mistake from China and
the Americans will have to come to
India's side this time because they need
India on their side against China. And
the Chinese economy may suffer
tremendous losses if they indulge in a
war, engage in a war with
India because we are we may not be that
powerful but we can certainly inflict
damage and we have some of the world's
deadliest
missiles. So um doesn't make sense for
China to start a war with India just to
bail Pakistan out. So then instead of
starting a war with India, can they send
supplies to Pakistan so that Pakistan
stays
afloat? Can they send those supplies in
such quantities at this time? Large
quantities. Pakistan is running out of
ammunition of arms, ammunition and all
that. They'll have to send tremendous
amounts of ammunition. When you are at
war with a country like India, if you're
Pakistan, you're going to be spending
incredible amounts of ammunitions.
ammunition, bullets, shells, rockets,
drones, all these little things every
day, right? You're going to need
tremendous quantities of this.
Otherwise, you're done. Can China supply
all that to Pakistan? I don't think they
can. They can send some, but not a
lot. Who else? Turkey. Turkey sent some
drones. They they wasted 400 to 500
yesterday. The Pakistanis.
Pakistan is in a deep deep situ bad spot
right now. It's it's difficult for the
Chinese even if they want to to bail
Pakistan out right
now. This is the opportunity that India
has needed has been waiting for for the
past 80
years. So the ball essentially is in
Pakistan's court. They need to step step
back
immediately otherwise two weeks maximum
and they're done. It's
over. Cynical says you mentioned how
absorbing Pakistan occupied Kashmir can
change our demographics forever and may
affect our national security. How do you
think this can play out realistically or
when it can happen? Look P can come back
in two weeks time maximum. Okay.
But the question you're raising is a
good question because I've mentioned
this
before. The people of
PUK they have been essentially part of
Pakistan for the past 70 80 years and
they probably identify as
Pakistanis and religiously they are they
of the Pakistani persuasion aren't they?
Uh and and they probably all will have a
tremendous amount of hatred for India
because of various reasons. Now, if you
take that territory and you absorb those
people into your population, it'll be a
culture shock for both
sides. It'll be a culture shock for both
sides. But I'm sure they can adapt. But
will that deep rooted hatred disappear?
That's the question. But we obviously
have Pakistanis living in India. We've
had Pakistanis, tens of thousands of
Pakistanis living illegally in India.
Pakistani women married to Indian
citizens for
decades. It worked, right?
So if you want it to work that way,
it'll work. Otherwise, we'll have to
decide what to do and how to deal with
the situation, right? We have a 100
million Bangladeshes living in India.
They all hate us, but they're living
among us. Work somehow in India.
Everything we make it work. What do we
call it? Jard. So we may even make this
work. P absorbed into India and u the
people of P becoming Indian citizens.
It will cause problems for a while. A
while as in like two three
generations. Okay. I've already
discussed the the Chinese air defenses a
lot. So let's take some other
questions. Uh Shriara Moli Moli Tadi
Nada says Iran has been offering to
mediate during this particular conflict
the India Pakistan war fifth war. Is
India is Iran a good actor or a bad
actor? Look, Iran is our friend. We we
should look at Iran as as our friend. We
have no no um issues with Iran. Uh the
Iranian foreign minister recently said
that you know Pakistan and India are
both brotherly countries for us. We are
neighbors. We have always been neighbors
and so on. So Iran would like to offer
its good offices to India and Pakistan
and act as a mediator and you know and
hopefully bring this conflict to an end.
And then the Iranian Iranian foreign
minister came to India. I think he was
in India yesterday or maybe today. I'm
not sure. So look
uh Mr. Foreign Minister is is very
welcome to come to India.
We will offer him the best of our
hospitality, the warmest welcome. But
when it comes to mediating between India
and Pakistan, uh
Iran now is not the time, right? This is
going to end the way it ends. uh we
appreciate Iran's friendship and
partnership and all that and we'll work
together with Iran but uh this this
attempt to mediate is is you know I'm
sure it is it comes from a good place
and they want to see peace between India
and Pakistan because we are all
brotherly nations which we are which we
are but look this is the wrong time to
do
that wait for two weeks then try to
mediate if there is any Pakistan left
but we appreciate Iran's offer and
Iran's Iran's
friendship for
sure.
Okay. What do we have? Um let us see.
Let us see. Let's
see. Okay. We have discussed the Chinese
air defense system adn
noseam.
Um okay. Red devil says you talk of
deportation of Bangladesh who came
during 1971 and their children. Does
this also include the Bengali Hindus who
are basically escaping a
genocide? No, it does not include
Bengali Hindus who escaped the genocide.
They are welcome to stay here
forever. I am talking about the
Bangladeshes who infiltrated into India
after Bangladesh became a separate
country, who infiltrated into India
illegally by crossing the borders.
That's what I am talking about. The
Bengali Hindus who fled from Bangladesh
fleeing for their lives in 1971 who
settled in India. They are our people.
They are welcome to be here forever. The
Bangladeshi infiltrators I have an issue
with is the ones who infiltrated into
India illegally after 71. Not during the
71 conflict. 71 war. Not them. Not them.
I have an issue with the illegal
infiltrators who came after 71. That's
the issue. They are the ones who are
illegally here. The Bangladeshi Hindus
who came in, we accepted them as
refugees and we allowed them to become
citizens. That happened legally as a
matter of state policy. I have no issue
with those people. I have an issue with
the illegals who came in later. They are
the ones who are dangerous to
us. Okay.
Okay, Mahesha says, "Is it possible to
neutralize a nuclear attack?" So, what
does a nuclear attack look like? A
nuclear attack is an attack that
involves a nuclear weapon. A nuclear
weapon
is not very large. I assure you, uh, how
much plutonium do you need for a nuclear
weapon? Look, I'll give you a ballpark
figure. 2 to three kilos. 2 to three
kilos of pluton plutonium. And plutonium
is a very dense metal. 2 to three kilos
of plutonium is like this
much. This much physically maybe smaller
than that. 2 to three kilos. It's so
dense that a very small quantity weighs
2 3 kilos. If you're talking about
uranium you may need roughly very rough
ballpark figure let's say 10 kilos to
have a kiloton kind of weapon. you know
10 20 kilo Hiroshima type weapon if you
have good technology you can make do
with 10 15 kilos of uranium or maybe two
to five kilos of plutonium that's the
nuclear uh file material and the warhead
itself is not going to be very large you
can essentially have a bomb in a
suitcase if it's
[Music]
plutonium so that's the warhead that's
the deliverable that needs to be sent to
the location the package that needs to
delivered to the location. So you need a
delivery mechanism for that which is
typically a missile or it is dropped as
a bomb from an aircraft. Now today if
the Pakistanis want to send an aircraft
to drop a bomb on an Indian city that
aircraft will be wiped out s long before
it reaches an Indian city because our
air defenses are are frighteningly good
these days. So they have two ways of
doing it. Either by launching a
ballistic missile or a cruise missile or
an aircraft launched missile, air
launched missile. Three options. Do the
Pakistani F-16s have the capability to
to launch missiles that can deliver
nuclear warheads? I'm not sure. Let's
assume they do. So we need to have the
capacity to take out those rockets
before they reach the destination. And
uh if it's a ballistic missile, we need
to be able to shoot down ballistic
missiles, which probably we can. If it's
cruise missiles, that's more difficult
because cruise missiles can fly low just
like aircraft and skim over the surface.
In which case, you have to be super vig
v vigilant. So, it's definitely possible
to neutralize a nuclear attack. The
Pakistan Pakistanis have been launching
missiles and drones the past 48 hours at
us. They have tried their best to hit
more than 20 25 Indian cities thus far
and they have failed every single time.
So we have excellent air defenses. They
haven't used ballistic missiles yet. If
they launch a ballistic missile, I think
before the missile reaches India,
Pakistan will be
flattened because ballistic missiles are
a red line. Uh so my answer is that it's
definitely very possible to neutralize a
nuclear attack. See, if there's a
ballistic missile incoming, then we have
multiple ways of killing it. One is the
S400 system that probably can take out
ballistic missiles, especially short and
medium-range missiles. The other one is
the Pritski air defense system, which
has a two-stage system. There's a rocket
that takes out the missile outside the
atmosphere. It's an exo atmospheric
interception. So, it intercepts the
incoming missile outside of the
atmosphere more than 100 km above the
surface of the Earth. If that
interception fails, there's a second
rocket that that goes up which takes out
the incoming missile about 40 kilometers
above the surface of the earth. That is
endoat atmospheric interception. So if
one fails, the other one will take it
out. And these are very accurate
missiles. So if there's an nuclear
missile coming in, a missile with a
nuclear payload coming in, if you take
it out outside of the atmosphere, then
even if the warhead falls down, it it
will probably be destroyed, right before
it reaches the earth. And yeah, it can
cause uranium contamination or whatever,
but that is not as bad as a nuclear
detonation. Even if the warhead is
destroyed 40 kilometers or 20 kilometers
above the surface of the Earth, it won't
result in a nuclear explosion.
Right. So it's definitely very possible
to neutralize a nuclear attack very much
so especially when you have good air
defense systems and these days we do
have very good air defense systems.
Remember in 2019 or whichever year it
was we carried out an anti-satellite
test ASAT test. So, we have a kill
vehicle, a rocket,
um, a missile which can take out
satellites outside of the Earth's or
atmosphere at a at an altitude of
between 200 to 1,000 km above the
Earth's surface. And typically, the
satellites that travel at about 10
kilometers per
second. 10 km/ second is faster than a
bullet. And we can take a satellite out
at that speed at that height. So that I
assure you can also take out an incoming
ballistic
missile. So worry not my friends worry
not. Geopolitical dub says are we
handling the information warfare better
this time? I think we are handling it
much better than 2019. when we did Bala
court you know the Pakistani information
warf had actually proved to be superior
they claimed that they took out I don't
know how many Indian aircraft at least
to this end and uh they have been able
to convince the world that we did not
shoot down one of their F-16s right they
have been able to push that narrative
and make that narrative win in
2019 and uh when the surgical strikes
happened they said what surgical strikes
nothing
happened there's no evidence this time
we have done things in such a way that
they can't deny anything. We did
multiple strikes on each terror
terrorist building, headquarters,
whatever. And we did not nearly strike
those things multiple times. We sent
drones to to film everything. And we've
put all the footage out in the public
domain. And then after the Pakistanis
tried to tried to strike back, the next
day we did daylight strikes all across
Pakistan in which the Pakistanis
actually filmed the drones coming down
and slamming into Pakistani
infrastructure. There were missile
strikes at night that were filmed. So it
has been very public this time.
It is very clear to everybody including
Pakistanis that India is winning this
and India has hit Pakistan struck
Pakistan at will multiple times and the
Pakistanis haven't been able to hit
back. The Pakistanis have claimed that
what they've taken out five Indian
fighter planes. Have they shown a single
piece of evidence? Do you think you can
hide such evidence in today's day and
age? Can you? It's very hard. Uh so this
time India has been very well prepared
and we are definitely winning the
information warfare and even in the
western media you know we seem to have
we seem to have allies this time most of
the western media is very anti-India
even today. So the best they can do
right now is to not cover the matter.
They're staying they're not covering the
IndiaPakistan war right now because
India is winning very very very
obviously winning what's happening thus
far. But there are some channels in
which you have uh certain journalists
who are absolutely roasting the the the
Pakistanis. There's this lady called
Yalda Hakeim who who's of Afghan origin.
She works for Sky Sky News or something.
I mean every day the new video clip of
our comes out you know roasting some
Pakistani taking some Pakistani diplomat
or foreign minister or defense minister
whoever it is to the absolute cleaners.
She's doing a great job that lady. So
overall this time the Pakistanis aren't
winning the information warfare thing
and there are certain uh US academics
there's this professor of political
science some insign insignificant fellow
who's married to a Pakistani woman who
is trying
to you know take the Pakistani side and
make it look like India is not doing
well not working this time it's not
working so it's a much improved
um information warfare performance from
India this time around much improved
much better and we are
clearly winning the the warfare this
time okay we have already dealt with
wartime blackouts I already took the
question so let's take some other
questions
um Sunumi says yes Yaldahhim is a gem
she certainly is she's doing a
tremendous job of being an ally of India
Okay. Grateful black says India should
give Kashmir back to Pakistan for peace.
Uh let me tell you something, Mr.
Grateful Black. India should end
Pakistan's existence for peace. And
that's what's going to happen. It's
happening in real time right now. Wait,
you must be a Pakistani. I I I feel
sorry for you. I have nothing against
the citizens of Pakistan. They're human
beings just like us. They are they are
our relatives. You people are our blood.
We're the same people. But blood doesn't
matter because only only culture
matters. You you may be our our blood
but you you want us dead, right?
Pakistan is most of you at least. I feel
sorry for you but and the best thing for
you is the end of Pakistan. The
bulcanization of Pakistan which is about
to happen. If Pakistan continues the way
it's continuing, it's it's trying to hit
Jammu and whatnot right now. Pakistan
will be balconized in the next 14 days
maximum. Then try to get Kashmir. What
Kashmir? Okay, we've discussed enough
nuclear
missiles. Ashish Singh says what will
Pakistan do now? Is there not able to to
penetrate the Akash air defense system?
Yeah, they have failed miserably at
at trying to penetrate the air defense
system that we have multi-layered air
defense system which of which the Akash
is the primary component as far as we
can understand thus far and it's been an
absolute superstar performance by the
Akash air defense system. The Pakistanis
are unable to penetrate. They're unable
to hit a single Indian target. They've
been
trying for the past 48 hours. Hundreds
of drones they've launched. Not worked,
right? What do they do
now? Well, if it doesn't work, what do
you do? You fall back on your tried and
trusted weapon of terrorism. So, they'll
try and launch terror strikes on India.
Maybe by trying to to to push terrorists
across the border. It's already been
tried last night and a whole bunch of
terrorists were taken out by the BSF
last night who were trying to cross over
into the Indian uh across the border
into the Indian territory and they could
try and uh activate sleeper cells from
inside India whe whether it is Rohingyas
or Bangladeshies or or Pakistanis or
cookies or whatever and they could do
terror strikes in India on Indian cities
that's always a possibility. So India is
going to be have to going to have to be
on high alert. These are the options
they have. Otherwise, they can try more
dangerous options, more dangerous for
them. Try cruise missiles or something.
If they try such more dangerous weapons,
you know, it's going to come back to
them like in in twice the number in
twice the twice twice the magnitude. So
the best thing Pakistan can do at this
point in time if they want to continue
to exist as a nation is to step down
immediately.
That's the first step. Second, dismantle
your terrorist infrastructure because
just stepping down is not going to be
enough
anymore. Just stepping down is not going
to be enough. You have to dismantle your
terrorists infrastructure. You have to
hand over the wanted terrorists to
India. All that otherwise you're done
Pakistan. You're
done. Okay. N says, "Do you think
Pakistan will deescalate the issue or
try to escalate this in order to get
some financial aid from the
world? Right now the question is no
longer of financial aid. The question
is the question from the military
perspective because it's the military
that that owns Pakistan. It's the it's
Pakistan is a military dictatorship.
Prime Minister is just for show. It's a
puppet." Right? From the military
perspective, I say this over and over
again, it's a question of survival.
Survival. Now, they have sold the
Pakistani public this
this
story that we are responsible. We we
guarantee the existence of Pakistan
because our great existential threat to
the east is India and only the Pakistani
military stands between India and
complete destruction of Pakistan. And
the social contract you have in Pakistan
is that you allow the military to rule
over the country as complete
dictators. In exchange for that, the
military saves us from
India when required. That's the social
contract.
So, so the entire legitimacy of the
Pakistani military hinges
on Pakistan being a on the military
proving itself to be able to defend the
country against India and defend itself
against India. In the past 48 48 50
hours, they have failed miserably at
that. They have not been able to prevent
India from striking at will and they
have been completely miserably been
unable to hit India at all.
So the military if this continues the
people will rise up against the
military. That's what happens in police
states in dictatorships when the
legitimacy goes away. The people rise up
because they have been oppressed. They
have been tolerating the
oppression for decades just because of
the social contract that the military
can oppress us but at least it will save
us from India and they hate India.
That's why they tolerate the military.
So now that the military has been shown
to be a failure, the Pakistani people in
the next few days will rise up against
the military. Yesterday there were all
these rallies in Pakistan asking for the
um release of Imran Khan from from from
prison. Right? So it's already you're
already seeing this on the streets of
Pakistan to some extent then Balojasthan
will rise up then Kaibar will rise up
and so on.
So, so the military has no choice but to
keep on escalating, but to keep on
trying to escalate otherwise their own
people will eat them alive. You
understand? There's going to be riots.
The riots will be directed at the
military. So, Pakistan is caught in a
terrible place. The military of Pakistan
is a caught is caught in a terrible
place. They have no choice but to try
and escalate
further. If
they step back then they have to step
down
also that's the issue right and they
won't step
down excuse
meager says once Pakistan breaks up
what's next for India internal issues
like illegal immigrants and sleeper
sales might escalate within the public
what should how should India tackle that
once Pakistan breaks up India is going
to have its hands full dealing with
Pakistan dealing with the break up of
Pakistan with these new countries coming
up Balojasthan
Sinduh and so on dealing with Kyber
Pakun who has integration with
Afghanistan dealing with what's left of
Punjab dealing with the reintegration of
Pakistan okay Jammu Kashmir Gilgit
Baltistan all of that is going to be a
huge process and there's going to be
possible problems within India because
of the millions of illegal immigrants
which we have
tolerated for decades so it's going to
be a difficult road forward
But you progress only through
difficulties, right? You get a go
towards a better future only by
navigating difficulties. And if you want
to have a better future in which
Pakistan is no longer a threat, then you
have to go through this phase. So we
will have to go through
it. Arnab Malik says people are
critically injured in Punjab. Okay,
we'll see about that and if it's true,
it's very unfortunate and the Pakistan
will pay the price for that if they have
done
that. Rug says why would Aim Moner, the
chief of Pakistan's military, why would
he attend the funeral of a known global
terrorist makes no sense because now the
fig leaf of plausible deniability is
gone. Pakistan has now openly admitted
that they are a terrorist nation. Their
defense minister went on Sky News was it
with Yaldah Haken? I think he went on
Sky News at least twice at least he he
gave at least two interviews to Western
media Pakistan defense minister in which
he stated very clearly very explicitly
that Pakistan has been doing the dirty
work for the west for decades for the US
for the UK and for the west dirty work
of terrorism and he said that if we had
not been doing this for the west then we
would have had a spotless record and
nobody would be able to point fingers at
us and call us terrorists.
He admitted this at least twice in two
different interviews. So it's open now.
And then even Bilawal Bhau the son of
Benazar BH who seems to have some
official position in the government. He
also said the same thing that we have
served as terrorist. We have served as
served as terrorist mercenaries for the
US and for the west. So this happens
only when your master has given you has
served you the divorce papers. Then you
can say bad things about your master.
Right? So now it's open. It's clear that
Pakistan has openly admitted that they
have been yes a terrorist nation. They
it's been part of their their state
policy. Terrorism is is a is a policy of
their
state. Now that it's in the open, what
difference does it make if Aim Munir
attends the funeral of terrorists,
right? So after the Indian strikes on
terrorist infrastructure apparently more
than a 100 terrorists died including the
brother of um these names I just don't
remember these names foreign names right
not our names um Hafi sed
aar masudazar one of these fellows one
of the the brothers of one of these
fellows the the brother of one of these
fellows who was involved in the murder
of Daniel Pearl so we India brought
justice to Daniel Pearl's family after
decades after he was killed. The
Americans didn't bring justice to Daniel
Pur's family. We did it right. So we
killed more than 100 terrorists
apparently and the Pakistani military
gave these terrorists a state funeral
with full military honors and
highranking Pakistani military officials
including apparently Asim Munir attended
this funeral. So now it is open in front
of the world that the Pakistani
military, the Pakistani ISI and the
Pakistani terrorist infrastructure they
are one and the same. They are the same
entity. This is the proof that the world
needs to see. It's the end of the story.
There's no more proving to be no more
proof to be given. It's
open. They are no longer hiding it.
So now if somebody asks India what's the
evidence Pakistan is a Pakistan is a
terrorist nation I mean what more
evidence do this people want
right okay
um Karan Alawad says according to you
what should India not do in this war
India should not be hasty give yourself
two
weeks take it easy next 2 three days try
to make
next two three days tell the world we
are trying to deescalate. We are giving
Pakistan the option to step back. We
know the Pakistanis cannot step back. We
know the Pakistani military has no
choice but to keep on trying to hit
India. But we should not hit any more
targets in Pakistan the next two three
days. So the world can so the world
should be able to see we gave them a
chance. Next three days we should do
this. So the next 3 days the Indian
media will be very unhappy that we are
not hitting
Pakistan
then or or before depending on how
Pakistan behaves. Then you go for the
kill because then by the time Pakistan
will be running out of ammunition and
munitions and the pressure will be very
high on the Pakistani
military. Um but if they hit some Indian
city or do something terrible before
that then we can wipe them out with full
impunity. So it will depend on their
actions. But if things continue as they
are right now, it becomes kind of a new
normal. Then we wait for 3 4 days before
taking the next step and the next step
eventually is going to be a pulse pause
thing whenever it happens. Make a sudden
quick move into Pakistan 30 40 50 km and
stop and then it'll be a further
humiliation for the Pakistan military
and then hopefully the people rise up
and throw them out otherwise we can
engineer it. So it's going to be a
matter of a couple of weeks if the
Pakistani military continues the way it
is doing right now. The only thing that
can save Pakistan at this point in time
is if they step down
completely immediately. That's the only
way Pakistan survives the next two
weeks. Otherwise it's
done. All
right. Rash God says what would Janeka
do in the situation? I just what I just
said that's what he would do.
Uh, okay. Once again, S400, it's not the
S400 that's being used. Uh, Anand
Chandak says, "Why are my comments not
getting posted?" Well, it just got
posted, that's why I took it. So, it's
not like
that.
Uh, okay. Some new questions, please.
Let's uh about the
situation. Apurva says, "Should India
reintegrate Balojasthan and or Synind
into India or make it a proxy? What's
the feasibility of a naval blockade? A
naval blockhead is is very feasible. We
can do that especially using submarines
which are way more dangerous than
surface vessels. A naval blockade is
very feasible if we need to do it.
Should we reintegrate Baljasthan and or
Sind into India? Not at this time. Not
at this time. They are a very
radicalized population and if we hastily
reintegrate them into India then it'll
cause lots of problems. I think we have
to give ourselves a timeline of maybe 50
years for the reintegration of the
entire subcontinent once Pakistan breaks
up. So there has to be a cooling down
phase. Um it's not like the case of
Bangladesh right in 71 Bangladesh had
been out of India for just 24 years and
there was no radicalization as such in
in the population of Bangladesh. Today's
Bangladeshi population is super
radicalized and that happened after 71
after their
independence. So in 71 it made sense for
India to reintegrate Bangladesh
immediately after just 24 years out
outside of
India. But Balojasthan Sind have been
out of India for almost 80 years.
They're culturally very different now.
Doesn't make sense for us to reintegrate
them immediately into India. We need to
let's say shepherd them over the next
few years or decades. We have to
dradicalize them through reforms of the
education system and other means. So it
doesn't make sense for us to reintegrate
them immediately if if and when Pakistan
breaks
up. Recent reports say that a drone fell
into a house in Lakhanur injuring
people. Will that boost India's further
action?
Okay, that's unfortunate if it's if it's
happened. But you know um
yeah, if if this has happened and if
people have been injured and if property
has been damaged or destroyed, Pakistan
will pay for it. So we have to be
patient for a few days and then the end
game starts if Pakistan doesn't step
down.
Okay. What else? What's the future of
Pakistan?
Look, Adita says, "What's the future of
P?" Uh, will will it? I think P will be
merged into India once Pakistan breaks
up pretty soon. I'm pretty sure about
that. Not Balojasthan, not Sinda, not
North Punjab, Pakistan and Punjab.
Definitely not Ky, Pakuna, but P and
Gilgit Baltistan will be
reintegrated.
Um, who has declared a full-blown war?
Have they declared the war? Pakistan.
Okay. In the past 2 hours, 3 hours, I'm
not sure. But probably PJK and Gilgit
Baltistan will be
reintegrated. We'll see about
that. White House has just said that the
president wants it to to deescalate.
Just 5 minutes back. Well, obviously
Donald Trump has to say these things
that we want this to deescalate. We
don't want the situation to to worsen.
He has to say these things. It's all
right. It's all right. We also want it
to deescalate. Please Pakistan, stand
down. Stop this nonsense. Stop lobbing
missiles and rockets and drones at our
civilians. Stand down immediately. We'll
deescalate. You You have to take the
step. We aren't the aggressors. Who's
lobbing drones and missiles and rockets
at at whom right now? Who is doing the
air defense? Who is doing the offense?
The Pakistanis are doing the offense. We
are doing air defense. So if somebody
has to deescalate it, it has to start
with
Pakistan. The problem is Pakistan can't
deescalate. That's the situation they
are
in
right. Rahul Shindai says what's the
role of drones in this war and how
powerful is India's drone system? You
know the past two years I've been
seeing look at what happened in
Azarbaijan the Armenia Azarbaijan war of
2020. Look at what's happening in the
Ukraine battlefield. Drones, loitering
munitions, suicide drones, kamicazizer
drones, AI, all of this is part of the
21st century warfare. India should not
be left behind. India's military needs
to integrate these things into its warf
fighting u scenarios and techniques and
see
today see today what happens what's
happening we use drones to to hit
Pakistan and we have excellent superb
anti- drone anti-missile anti-
everything systems so clearly those of
us who sit in sofas and talk about
things we don't know what the Indian
armed forces are actually doing so kudos
to the Indian armed forces kudos to in
government. We have not been left behind
in the 20th century way of doing war. We
are fighting a 21st century war here.
Outstanding. Outstanding. I'm so
pleased. I'm so pleased. So yeah, drones
have a very big role in this and I
really appreciate what the Indian armed
forces are doing and what the government
is doing by ensuring the armed forces
have the right tools at their disposal
to deal with
Pakistan and whoever else.
Is Pakistan breaking up guaranteed if a
in case a war happens sir a war is
happening right now? We are at a state
of war. It may not have been declared
officially but we are in a state of
war and Pakistan if it doesn't step back
right now immediately. If this continues
for two weeks it's breaking up is
guaranteed.
Guaranteed. Okay. Um let's see what what
what else do we
have?
Um Aditya Bali says what's your opinion
on the alleged news that Balojasthan
declared independence. Look people on
social media will say we have declared
independence and we we should support
that but there is no entity like there
is no actual entity called Baloistan.
It's just people right see Pakistan is a
nation whether you like it or not and
they have a government. So when Pakistan
says something it means the government
said something but when you say that
Balojasthan declared something there is
no entity called Balojasthan today the
chief minister of Balojasthan is a
Pakistanis isn't he today so when you
hear on social media Balojasthan is
declaring independence that means
various people from who belong to
Balojasthan or Baloi are declaring their
desire for independence or maybe the
Balojasthan liberation army which is a
freedom uh struggle organization maybe
they have declared independence
So that's what it means and we need to
welcome this we need to encourage them
and we need to if poss our government if
possible if it's possible we need to
support them in some way um through
whatever way through maybe Afghanistan
the Afghans are our friends right we
have a very good understanding with
Taliban maybe through Iran maybe not
through Iran but definitely Afghanistan
can help us out so
um so yeah you see that on social media
every day you see it right now I'm sure
that somebody from Baluchasan is saying
that we are independent from Pakistan
So we Indians should support that and my
opinion is that this needs to happen.
The actual independence and and uh
dissociation of Balojasthan from
Pakistan needs to
happen. Pawan HR education says what
will happen when Indian army marches
towards Islamabad and on the other hand
Baljasthan declares independence and
many activities happening. What will
happen to nuclear weapons and all that?
Look the way to disintegrate Pakistan is
not for India to go to Islamabad.
The way to have Pakistan disintegrate is
to have this war continue longer so that
the Pakistani munitions get
depleted and and the Pakistani army is
shown to be completely important
ineffective to its people and then you
the situation becomes ripe for a revolt
from within Pakistan of the people who
are tired of army operation.
So we have to condition create those
conditions and we have to encourage
those conditions of Pakistan and
Pakistan it's breakup has to happen from
within inside from inside of
Pakistan not with us marching to
Islamabad we need to engineer this
remotely that's what needs to happen and
we can obviously take military action in
strategic ways to surgically start
splitting Pakistan into pieces And we do
it without hurting the civilians as far
as possible. Obviously, it's going to be
very strategic. It has to be done very
strategically. We don't march on
Islamabad. We don't march on any major
city. We do it in a such a way that it
happens from inside by simply making the
military completely ineffective,
completely important, completely
helpless and in such a position that
they can't even withstand their own
people's fury. That's what needs to
happen. That's that's how you
disintegrate
Pakistan. Swapnil says good to see you
Swapnil. Why was Cindi not split into
two parts like Punjab and Bengal? Why so
many Cindi Hindus live when so many
Cindi Hindus live there? God knows so
many Cindi Hindus were made homeless
right after 1947 after partition. Um it
it I think the decisions were m these
decisions of what lines will be on the
map and how they'll be uh split. These
decisions were made by people who had no
connection with India or who didn't care
about India. Mainly it was Siril
Radcliffe the British uh individual who
arbitrarily drew lines on the map very
very arbitrary lines. Why? Why? I mean
if you look at uh
Bangladesh, why is Silad part of
Bangladesh? It was a Hindu majority
region. Why was Chittagong Chagram part
of Bangladesh? It should never have been
part of Bangladesh and so on. So so many
such injustices were done and they were
done by the British
and aided and abetted by our
so-called freedom fighters and leaders
of that time. You know that's how it
happened.
Ursa Miner says, "I live in Rome and I
have friends from Pakistan. The
narrative in their media then the
narrative in their media hasn't
recognized most attacks on their country
and is extremely defensive. When do you
think the true facts will come to
light?" Yeah, the Pakistanis I I believe
imposed a internet blackout in Pakistan
yesterday. That's what I heard
yesterday. Um so their media will spin a
certain narrative. Their media obviously
is beholden to the ISI military
terrorism complex. So they have to keep
on pushing the propaganda to their own
people that we are
winning. They'll do it as long as is as
as is possible. So we're going to have
to break it by creating facts on the
ground by so the Indian government will
have to do it. The Indian military will
have to do it from far without putting
too much boots too far into the ground.
Um so yes their media narrative is very
different from what's actually
happening.
Right? So the facts will come to light
the longer this goes on. Right now it's
just 48 plus maybe less slightly less
than 72 hours into the war. Right? One
week into the war it's going to be a
different scenario. If it goes 2 weeks
it's going to be endame for Pakistan. So
by that time the media won't be able to
hide what's really happening. So the
longer this continues the harder it will
be for their media to lie to their own
people. And yeah that's just how it
goes. It's it's often a war of
narratives. All right.
Um okay. Okay. Okay. Do we have any
other
question? Any other interesting
questions? Amisha Misha says, "Are the
Arab countries with us?" I assure you
the Arab countries are with us. Um the
major Arab countries. Saudi Arabia
doesn't want anything to do with
Pakistan. Pakistan used to be of use to
them in the past. No longer the case.
They rather very much would prefer to do
business with India. We are on very good
terms. You can it's unbelievable how
much things have changed in the past 10
11 years with visav our relationship
with the Gulf countries. We are on
excellent terms with Saudi Arabia with
the UAE
uh with Oman and so
on. Yeah. So the Arab countries are with
us. I assure you about that they are
with us and it's a great
thing. AJ Pillah says I think Baljasthan
after liberation will have border issues
with Iran, Afghanistan and Punjab or
Pakistan. Yeah, you know these once when
new countries emerge out of out of old
countries these issues happen. So we're
going to have to be the mediator in this
and ensure that things are done properly
not unlike not like what happened in
1947 when arbitrary lines were drawn on
the map. Right? So, we're going to have
to ensure that everybody gets justice
and nobody uh feels like, you know,
they've been robbed of some territory or
something. So, we're going to have to
ensure that happens when it
happens. Okay, I've taken I think most
questions now. Uh geopolitical dub says
will or should India continue to
weaponize water or any other means to
create panic in Pakistan? Look, if
Pakistan disintegrates in the next two
weeks as is very possible, then we don't
then we no longer have to do anything
about water because there's no Pakistan
anymore. Then we are dealing with Punjab
separately, Baloistan separately, Sinda
separately. And we don't want to hurt
the people, right? We don't want to hurt
the people. This was about punishing the
evil military ISI terrorist entity. It's
not about hurting the people. We don't
want to hurt the people. So if Pakistan
disintegrates, end of story. we'll have
new uh a new treaty with all these all
these
countries. But if uh yeah, so it it
depends on how things go in the next two
weeks. All right. Okay. So, I'm going to
end today's live stream over here and
we're going to do another live stream
tomorrow in which I'll take some more
questions from the comments and also
some questions from the live chat. So,
yeah, this was a very long live stream,
3 hours almost 10 minutes. So, thank you
so much for the questions. It was really
fun, very interactive and you all asked
great questions live in front of us and
yeah, let's continue this tomorrow. All
right, I'm sure things will have changed
to some extent tomorrow or not. We'll
see. All right, thank you so much until
then until tomorrow. Take care and I'll
see you very soon. Thank you. Bye-bye.